What's up?
What's going on?
It's me, Ryan.
From the local store.
Cheers.
We need a prediction here.
Guys!
Will I reach credits today?
Yes or no?
What do you think?
You think I can do it?
Are you feeling it?
Are you pushing it in?
Are you working your body?
Because if you're not, you're doing it wrong.
Although, I do have a confession.
I did not work my body.
In fact, I did the opposite.
Dude, I had this drink in the freezer shortly before.
So it become extra cold.
Oh, yeah.
Guys, I'm fucking nervous today.
Guys, I don't know why.
I'm just... You think I can do it?
Can I reach credits?
Oh, man.
Do I got it?
A good old Jägermeister gonna do it.
I don't have any of those.
Oh, my God.
I feel weird, man.
Okay, you know what?
That's enough of that.
Let's get into the game, shall we?
Here we go!
I'm kidding.
We're not doing that again.
Come on!
I'm kidding.
We're not doing it.
That's so... Imagine if I then did it now.
Imagine if I actually transition over to...
You know.
Wrong button.
Sorry, I didn't mean to do it again.
That was the wrong button.
Wrong button.
Let me click the transition button.
Let's see what happens then.
We're actually in Minecraft.
But there's no sound.
Oh, there's sound.
Okay, never mind.
What's going on, guys?
Are you happy?
Ah...
Nice.
Guys!
I was actually gonna stream yesterday.
And the day before.
But then I decided to get into, like, a...
Like, I was already feeling better at that time.
Like, I wasn't really sick anymore.
But I was really obsessed with Lord of the Rings.
And I wanted to watch all of it.
And I did.
And...
You know what?
I did something...
That some may consider heretical.
But...
I think I'm a changed man.
Regarding something.
I posit the following.
Now, I will preface this.
I was always a fan of the extended editions of Lord of the Rings.
And if you had to have a marathon, you would watch the extended editions.
You know?
No question.
But then I was like...
You know what?
I kind of forgot what the theatrical versions were like.
Haven't seen them since...
Well, the theaters.
So I decided to put them on.
And you know what?
They are so superior...
To the extended editions.
People have been fed a lie!
Why?
The extended editions contain so many shitty fucking scenes...
That don't make sense.
It's way better!
To watch the theatrical.
That's my opinion.
I will die on that hill now.
The pacing is just so much better.
I had to say it, man.
I don't know if you know anybody who's exactly like that.
You know, you gotta watch the extended edition.
Because I used to be like that.
And now I'm changed.
There it is.
I said it.
I had to get it out.
Oh, I feel better.
It's like a burden off my shoulders.
Man, oh man.
Average ADHD guy's opinion?
I don't know.
I think it's just like a standard...
Movie enjoyer's opinion.
I think all of you forgot what the theatrical versions were like.
You just don't remember.
You know?
Speaking of ADHD...
I actually...
I went to the doctor again.
To ask for a second opinion on that.
And they told me they would get back to me.
A different doctor.
So let's see.
Maybe something will come of that.
Or not.
We'll see.
Because...
I kid you not.
Like, I was watching a YouTube video yesterday.
On my TV.
Now that I have a TV, I can watch stuff on that, right?
And it was a video from Fern.
It's like a documentary type channel, right?
And I shit you not.
Like, I probably re-watched the first two minutes of that video.
Six times.
Because I kept getting distracted by something.
And I didn't pay attention to what he was saying.
And it seemed important to know.
So I kept going back six times.
First it was like, oh, Jackie's here.
Let me just, you know, cuddle her a little bit.
Oh, fuck.
What did he say?
Go back.
And then I was like, okay, I'm gonna quickly grab something from the fridge while it's playing.
And then I got distracted.
Oh, fuck.
Go back.
Like, I didn't pay attention.
Six times, dude.
Crazy.
Is that weird?
Relatable?
Okay.
I will say, though, that video in particular also...
You really had to pay attention.
Because there was so much info dump really fast.
Will there be more secret deadlock streams?
Maybe.
Honestly, maybe there will also be more StarCraft streams and World of Warcraft streams.
I don't know about secret, but definitely like...
Non-mainstream style content that I do.
So it's more like...
Me being completely...
Almost lying down horizontally, you know, and playing.
We're talking ultra-mega-relaxed.
Because, uh...
When Wrath of the Lich King anniversary comes out, I'll probably jump back in, man.
We'll see.
Oh my god!
Crunchy Enchilada!
Thank you for the subs, man.
That's ten subs right there.
Thank you.
Wow.
That sounds delicious.
Crunchy Enchilada.
Mmm.
Now I want to eat that.
Speaking of food...
I think I realized, guys, that I may have a toxic relationship with food.
Have you guys come to that realization, too, quite late in your life?
It's like, I was watching this documentary about...
Um, what was it?
This weight loss...
Uh, thing that came out, you know what I mean?
On Kurzgesagt.
And...
The whole description of it, I was just like, damn, I fucking relate to this?
Thinking about food all the time, you know?
Like, that's all my mind is circling about.
It's just food, food, food.
So maybe I should try and cut back on some of those pleasures, you know?
Gee whir!
Thank you for the five subs!
Who got it?
Angelo.
Ex-Lord Ahmed.
Chunky Chip...
Wait!
Chunky Chipmunk!
So we have, uh...
Chunky Enchilada and Chunky Chipmunk.
No, no, wait.
That was Crunchy Enchilada.
Sorry.
I got it wrong.
Also, I just accidentally alt-tapped into the game.
Now I can see you.
I'm so fuck-happy?
Hmm.
Okay.
Got it.
What if I switch to, uh...
Doki Doki now?
Yeah.
Now that would be the ultimate fake-out, wouldn't it?
Ha!
Well, what if I do it, like, half an hour into this?
Like, I just quit the game and be like, here we go.
Guys?
It's gonna come at some point today.
Will it be in two minutes?
Five minutes?
Ten minutes?
Thirty minutes?
It'll happen out of nowhere when you least expect it and you...
when it makes you the most mad.
Just you wait.
I have it all planned out.
It's scripted to perfection.
I'm like, uh...
Walter White in the lab, you know?
Preparing the ultimate concoction for maximum rage bait.
Oh my god.
Jeeber!
Thank you so much, man.
Five more subs.
Congrats to the people that got that.
Don't worry, we're gonna get Doki Doki later.
Poop particles!
Guys, why are you gifting so many subs right now?
Thank you so much.
I feel like poop particles is something that I would say.
I think I've said that before.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's play some Minecraft, shall we?
Hold on.
Oh my god, dude!
I'm in the end!
Right?
That's where I...
I can't believe I left it there.
That's crazy.
Okay, here we go.
Cheers.
Please reply to my tweet.
Oh my god, you can tell how aged this is.
New Dawn.
Man, last time was on the 17th.
That's 10 days ago.
That's crazy.
Wowie.
The dragon shall die.
Fuck!
I tried to put out the Doki music!
To mess with you, but I fucked it up.
Aw, man.
Damn it.
I messed it up.
I did.
Would have been funny, though, if I didn't mess it up.
Oh shit, what's happening?
Oh my god!
Wait a minute.
Uh, we may have to go back.
My pickaxe is in the shitter, guys.
Oh, I can't believe this.
Really?
Now?
Of all times?
Oh my...
Wait, how do I go back?
Oh, wait a minute!
I can't go back!
Oh, no!
Wait, do I have...
Tell me I have something.
I don't have any wood!
Is it just me, or is the game, like, insanely loud?
Holy crap.
Let's just pull that down a bit.
Test, test, test.
Oh my god.
Why is it so loud?
There we go.
Ah...
Jesus!
Wait a sec.
What is going on here?
Why is the damn game suddenly so loud?
Like, the effects and stuff is like...
I can't...
I can't dig this with my...
Shit.
Do I have any wood?
Guys, I'm actually kind of in trouble here.
Uh, wait.
Tell me the portal is open!
Okay.
Oh, I may have to defeat the dragon to enter this.
I don't remember.
No!
It's not even open!
They were cooked?
I can't do anything!
I can't believe this!
Do I have sticks or something?
I actually cannot believe this.
What about the little...
Isn't there a little portal to...
The other place?
Maybe we can...
Oh, but that's not gonna...
Oh...
Dude, I don't actually know what to...
I think I'm cooked!
I have to die!
I have to kill myself!
What else can I do?
Like, I can't do anything!
This is insane!
Uh...
I can't even get up there!
I...
No.
I am so completely lost!
I don't...
I don't know what to do!
Like...
I can't kill the dragon?
Or maybe I can.
Wait.
I do no damage!
Oh my god, bro.
Okay.
I have to die.
Kill me!
Kill me.
I literally can't do anything.
That is insane.
What on earth...
Am I supposed to do?
Now I have to find my...
Oh, this is just the worst?
I was so ready to kill this dragon!
It's ogre!
I can't get out!
Oh my god!
Dude, I'm not even kidding!
This is almost...
We have to restart a new world situation.
This is so incredibly fucked up!
How do I get out of...
Like, I'm fucked?
It's completely over!
Also, hold on.
Is the...
Options...
Sound...
Well, I'm gonna ask you guys something.
Is the...
Right before when I was complaining about the game being...
Very loud...
Was it loud for you too?
Hold on, I'm gonna hold that.
How was the audio like when I was yelling about that?
I'm tweaking?
Really?
No!
Sounded normal?
Okay.
All right, got it.
Any other issues?
All right, I mean...
This would be the perfect time to switch over to Doki Doki Literature Club.
Dude, in the preview on OBS on the other screen, it looks like it's lagging right now when I...
Actually, I just noticed this.
Is it lagging for you guys?
Like, is there a low framerate?
Hold on.
No?
What the hell is going...
Like, something's off here.
There is something going on.
Okay, whatever.
You guys say it's fine.
I trust you.
It looks like shit on my preview over there.
I don't know what's happening.
It's like it's running in 20 frames per second or something.
Like, I'm not freaking kidding here.
Like, I feel like this is a start a new world situation.
I can't even get out of this building I'm in.
Wait, there is a way.
I know how to do it.
I need to find my bed.
I hate to do this.
We have to die with no bed.
Jackie?
What are you...
What are you doing?
She was scratching the door.
It's a very smooth door, so she couldn't really scratch it.
So it's more like...
Uh, where are the enemies?
I just need to die right now.
Here we go.
Kill me.
I can't...
I can't do anything.
This is like the worst situation I've ever been in in Minecraft.
I'm not even kidding.
Wait, it doesn't matter.
It's fine.
I know which way to go.
I did this last time.
Wait, why can't I...
Something's wrong with my jumping now.
Why does my character not jump normally?
Huh?
Oh, is it this?
God!
Dude!
There's something going on.
It's wrong.
It's all wrong.
It's like everything is cursed.
Also, where am I?
Okay, so...
That way.
This is the worst situation ever.
I've never been in a worst spot in Minecraft.
In all the 700 hours I've played.
This has to be the worst.
It's insanity.
I also can't sprint.
Like, how does it go so wrong?
I'm supposed to kill the dragon!
And then I have to die twice, lose all my items, and I...
I probably can't even find my way back now, because I don't remember shit.
Jumping is cursed.
The music is...
Weird.
Dif...
I...
Oh, actually, it's not weird.
I guess it's just a new track.
From Creative, I guess.
It's all wrong.
This is not...
This is not the way it should be!
The script was different.
Clearly, right here, it says...
Oliver defeats the dragon...
In spectacular fashion.
Followed by applause.
And...
And yet...
This happened.
Wait, let me see.
Bro, I'm pretty sure I went west.
I'm pretty sure it was west of here.
God, I hope I'm right.
I don't...
Oh, wait, I do remember this, maybe.
Do I?
It's a good place to go, though, to get some resources.
For the journey.
Maybe they have some food.
I like this song, though.
Like...
Minecraft is actually so dependent...
On having...
A pickaxe.
So much so that...
If you don't have a pickaxe, but you have everything else...
You're cooked!
Can't do anything!
Who would have thunk?
Mining is important in Minecraft.
Wow.
That is insanity.
This is like the last thing I expected.
I really did...
Not expect this.
Oh, is that...
Oh, it's this guy.
I was about to say there's Detroit's everywhere.
But I forgot the name of them.
What are they called?
They're fucking armadillos.
Detroit!
I have Detroit on my brain.
Oh, no.
What the hell am I talking about?
Come on.
Hey, look!
Look!
The door's open!
I've been here!
Beautiful.
Oh!
Is that...
That has to be the island.
These guys are smoking grass.
You can see it.
There we go.
I don't want the rest.
Come on.
More bread.
Also, I need a bed.
I'm gonna steal one from these guys.
If I can.
May I also have to take this.
This is food.
Let me do this.
Uh, this.
And then I have to find a bench.
I don't think they have a bench here.
We should go punch a tree.
Also, where are the beds at?
How are there no beds?
Maybe down here.
Man, this couldn't have gone worse.
This is...
The absolute...
Like, this game is hard, man.
Frickin' Minecraft is...
Insane.
Oh!
Sweet!
Don't tell me it breaks.
Okay, good.
Take it out.
I need this.
Frick!
Oh, 48 as well.
That's amazing.
And I don't think I need anything else.
I can make my way to my base without anything else.
Um, that's west.
Yeah.
Let's just...
I know exactly where my base is.
I can even sprint now, because I have...
Oh, I should probably sleep.
Cheers.
What is this thing?
Mangrove Propagool.
What a weird name.
Nobody even knows what that means.
If you ask anyone, they will say, What is that?
I refuse to believe that anyone knows what that means.
So, according to my calculations, we should be home in about seven minutes.
Don't be risky.
I'm armed with a Propagool.
Don't come close.
I will shove it up your nose.
Imagine how uncomfortable that would be.
If someone just takes one of these Mangrove Propagools and puts them up your nose.
That's horrible.
Like, it looks like it's close, right?
That island over there?
But it's actually so far away that you cannot even comprehend it.
Like, I can't.
You may say...
Oh, is it like 30 or 100 or 5,000 blocks?
It's more.
You never want to swim if you don't swim fast.
Dude, maybe just make a boat, actually.
That's easy, right?
Why didn't I think about this?
I have to take the whole tree.
You know how it is.
There we go.
Yeah!
Let's go!
Okay, so that's north.
And my base should be about over there.
Pretty easy.
The good news is, every time I need to find my base, all I have to do is to destroy my bed and die.
That's an easy way home.
Pretty smart.
Or maybe I'll use one of those skulls you can have in your offhand.
So that when you die, you don't lose your items and you go send back to home or spawn, you know?
That's also smart.
Could have done that too.
Wait, was it here?
No.
Well, I don't remember this mountain.
But it should be about over there.
This tree I remember, though.
The lone tree.
I feel like I remember that crime up there.
Okay.
You know what?
Here's the plan.
I was wholly unprepared for what was going to occur in the end.
So here's the plan, okay?
We're gonna prepare even more.
That's right.
We're going omega crazy now.
We're going to use the digging machine and we will find...
You guessed it.
Netherite.
We will go there with Netherite.
Because I...
That was just too embarrassing.
Like, it was horrible.
Absolute tragedy.
I will be flattening the entirety of the Nether.
I will bend the world to my will.
Or hell.
Really.
Wait a minute.
No, never mind.
Yeah, those are the mountains back there.
I know exactly where my home is.
Get up.
Oh, wait.
I don't have an axe.
How do I...
Okay, there we go.
I did it.
Oak boat.
Hey, friend.
We should be about one minute from home.
You'll see.
There it is.
I'm so good.
The little Danish cow island is actually the perfect indicator to find my home.
Because they are kind of rare, those islands, you know?
So if you find that one, you know with almost full certainty that it's near home.
Look at the way it's spinning.
And then sometimes it's stopping.
Like that.
Because it's emptying its bladder.
That's the way I think about it.
Or maybe it's puking.
It's spinning so much, you know, it's getting a little sick.
What's up, guys?
Jillian.
I think your name was.
And Jimothy somewhere else.
And we also have a Jimberley hiding out somewhere.
Anyway, let's see here.
We got a shovel.
We bring the bed.
We got a golden helmet.
We need that.
And what about...
Oh my god.
The pickaxe is almost destroyed.
No!
I don't have enough diamonds!
Oh my...
Oh...
I...
You know what?
Guys, I feel like I am just not equipped to deal with the bait.
Like, it feels like I'm trying to run before I can walk in this world.
You know, like, I'm limited by these basic things that I just really should have.
And I don't have them.
It's embarrassing.
Now, the boat, I think I'd keep that.
Yep.
Don't even have any armor!
I guess we'll make some iron armor.
Arm...
Let's make one of these.
That one.
And this one.
Bop, bop, bop.
Lovely.
And then a shield.
I don't have it.
Let's make one.
Uh, that's just wood.
Pretty easy.
Speaking of wood, I should just have some on me like that.
Okay.
Then we need an axe.
I think we can...
Hey, wait a minute.
We can make a sword out of this, uh, diamond.
But should I?
Yeah.
I think I should.
This will be my new weapon.
Uh, da-da-da-da.
That would be sticks and stones.
Mine jack.
It's inside of me.
Make one of these.
Let's make an iron axe.
And I guess we're gonna make an iron pickaxe too.
Perhaps even, uh, two of them.
Maybe three.
No, two.
Two is good.
We're gonna go find some, uh, diamonds first.
Oh, and we lost all the freaking levels we had as well.
What a disaster.
Really.
The good news is we can make some bread here and this will be the main source of sustenance for today.
Very nice.
That's a lot of food.
Crafting table is good to have.
Oh, wait a minute!
I should make, uh, more toolboxes.
I always complain about this.
Oh god, that's all kinds of shit.
So golden sheets.
Hmm.
I can make three of them, I guess.
Then we need cocks.
Do I have them?
Can I make smaller cocks out of this?
Cog.
Shafts and wood.
Shaft, shaft, shaft.
Make a shaft, I need what?
Andesite alloys.
That's in here.
Oh, no, I don't have any of those either!
Crap.
Okay, maybe I, I say, whatever to the toolboxes for now.
It's fine.
I'll survive.
We're just gonna go find some diamonds, that's it.
It's not complicated.
There we go.
Infinity bow.
One arrow.
Crafting table is good to have.
Sticks.
Uh, we can leave these at home because we bring wood.
We're not gonna overthink this, we're just gonna do what needs to be done.
No bullshit.
No detours, no getting distracted, we're just gonna do it.
Like my son, Ben.
He will come and do you.
More sticks.
There we go.
And then we need coal.
Uh, torch.
There we go, look at that, that's a lot of torches, that's wonderful.
Uh, I really should make this survival checklist, I don't think I ever did.
Good.
These sheets, we don't need them anymore.
We're only gonna pick up the essentials too.
Yeah.
Really does suck though, that we can't, uh, bring a diamond pickaxe.
It's gonna be slow going here.
Yeah, but it's fine.
I mean, we're just finding diamonds.
And when we find diamonds, we can just make a diamond pickaxe down there and keep digging.
It's not gonna be enchanted, but, you know, it is what it is.
Uh, I'm tired of this cave over here, especially when it comes to diamonds.
I feel like it's shit.
It doesn't really help.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I need to make a compass that points to my home.
Let's see if we can't do that.
We need a respawn anchor for that, I think.
Glowstone and...
Really?
Crying obsidian?
That's what I need.
Oh, I have it.
Sick.
Glowstone...
I don't think I have glowstone, unfortunately.
Wait, I can make it.
One, two, three.
Oh!
Oh, I was hoping for some new stuff.
I mean, that is new, but still.
Okay.
So, I need a compass.
Wait, how does this work again?
I forgot.
Wasn't it in the achievements?
Somewhere.
Was it in...
here?
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, shit.
I made the wrong one.
I need lodestone.
Oh, I don't even know how to make it.
Oh, no.
No.
I don't know how to make it.
Oh, shit.
Balls.
Okay, but, I guess a compass is still good to have.
Let's just bring it.
At least it'll take us home to, you know, spawn.
That's something.
I gotta find the right ingredients to make the lodestone, man.
Wait a minute, maybe I can make it.
Oh, I thought maybe I had my inventory open, but I had to have the crafting table open, but that wasn't it.
All right.
Cool.
Are we ready?
I think we're ready.
Let's go.
Hostel Avista.
I'm going...
Let's do south.
God, I can't wait to make trains, man.
It's been...
It'll never happen.
It seems like it's so close, yet so far away.
What a tragedy.
Ah, okay.
The good news is, our items in the end should be preserved.
Because it's not gonna tick down, unless we go in there.
So whenever we come back there, we're gonna grab all our shit, and it's gonna be fine.
It's just in stasis right now.
It doesn't really matter.
Kind of want to go to a new biome first.
Just to maximize...
Oh, man.
Where did I find many diamonds?
Wasn't there, like, a specific...
Oh, let's try this cave, actually.
Oh, man.
I should have brought a spyglass.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Actually...
No, no, no.
It's fine.
I had some ideas, but I abandoned them in my mind.
Wait, is this the same cave that's connecting?
Maybe.
Could be.
Hallelujah!
Oh, my God.
This is actually kind of dangerous, because if there's a creeper down here, I wouldn't have known, and I could be dying, you know?
Dude, I need...
night vision potions.
Oh, it is the same cave.
Aw, man.
Okay, let's just go in the opposite direction than over here and see how far the cave stretches.
I see diamonds, actually, so that's perfect.
Also, weirdly, no creatures here.
Even though it's very dark and all that.
That's interesting.
Why am I so bad at Minecraft today?
Holy shit, I can't even move.
Like, it's just been disaster all the time.
Where did I see those diamonds?
Up here?
Yeah, there they are.
Oh, my God.
Okay, that's nice.
One more diamond and we can make a pickaxe.
Wow, that's really the end of that cave, huh?
Alright, guess I'm out.
No, I'm going this way.
Nah, I'm out.
I'm out.
Take me home.
Sweet home, Alabama.
Wait, I...
This is horrible.
Guys, I have a good feeling.
Watch this.
We're going to dig this way and something amazing will happen.
You're not going to believe it until you see it.
Oh.
Very nice.
Air hole.
Please break it in time!
Oh!
I couldn't see the progress.
Oh, my God.
I thought I was dead again.
We're fine.
What the hell?
Oh, wait.
I can breathe here!
Oh, my God.
I...
That's right.
I know all the Minecraft tech.
Wait, this is going to...
Dude, I'm so bad at Minecraft today!
This way.
Bubbles?
I should have brought the diving helmet.
Easy to say in hindsight.
Okay, let me...
Let me, uh...
Sit here and...
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no.
We're in trouble.
We're in trouble!
Go back!
How come I couldn't dig fast?
I was on the floor.
That should allow me to dig faster.
Oh, my God!
You know what?
Cheers.
Holy shit.
Nah, it's...
I'm out!
Nope.
Dude, I'm gonna end up dying.
Give me a fucking arrow!
This...
Dude, fuck.
We're starting over, dude.
New world.
New world, dude.
I...
I can't do this.
I am so...
I am so tempted to start a new world.
This world is cursed.
Oh, my God.
I hate it.
I can't...
Like, what is wrong with...
Like, it's like I lost all my skills in Minecraft.
Minecraft.
What a disaster.
Bro, I don't even want to go back!
I can't find my items!
This is the worst.
Minecraft...
Maybe too hard for me.
Like, I'm getting to that age where this game is just too hard.
I can't win.
I don't even care about my...
I'm sprinting.
I don't care.
I know where my home is.
We're sprinting.
And give me some...
God damn music!
Oh!
Thanks!
Okay, that's better, actually.
Much better.
Ah.
Also, I'm gonna turn this up just a bit.
Oh, the Danish cows!
I may actually go over there and just absolutely slaughter every cow on the island in anger.
It'll be a complete eradication of them.
I'm gonna do it with a smile on my face and everything.
The women and the children, too.
Younglings shall be slain en masse.
Like, the worst part is I don't even have enough iron to make new tools!
I wanna cry, man.
Wow.
You know what the worst part about this is?
Like, I was ready to frickin' kill a dragon!
Not 20 minutes ago!
And be, like, showered in experience and we're gonna fuckin' have a party and we're gonna be flying in the Elytra!
Instead, I'm back here in the middle of bumfuck nowhere!
With no tools, no armor, no food, nothing.
I don't wanna be in Alabama!
And yet, here we are.
But let's not forget what Confucius said back in the day when he found himself in a similar situation.
He said, fuck it.
Shit happens.
And you know what?
He's right.
Let's not overreact to this.
Let's just take it slow.
This is just a natural part of the world, you know?
You can't have, uh, ups without the downs.
Uh.
Right.
This is where I was...
You know what?
Let me make a vote.
I'm getting weird deja vu right now.
I'm not sure I like it.
Dude, should I leave part of this tree behind in, I don't know, frustration?
No.
We cannot break, you know, the rules.
Even in this situation.
Make the damn boat.
You know what?
No.
Break the...
Take it.
It's okay.
You know what?
We're not in a hurry.
That's right.
I'm just gonna kick back and enjoy this song.
Watch the sunset over the lonely tree.
TLT, by the way.
Niagara Falls, all that.
When you look at this, it's not that bad, you know?
Like, everything's fine.
And there's no way I'm going back for those items that I just lost.
I will not...
Like, I will never go swimming again.
Just like real life, being in water sucks.
I hate going swimming.
It's terrible.
Humans were not made for water.
That's my opinion.
And you know what else my opinion is?
Non-extended versions of Lord of the Rings are superior.
I will say it again in 49 minutes.
Many hills to die on today.
Oh my god.
Hmm.
It should be right over...
Wait a minute.
I wasn't fully paying attention.
Oh wait, I know where I am.
I know where I am.
Yeah.
You see this disgusting rock over there?
That's north of my base.
Really should have just made the base exactly on my spawn.
That would make sense.
Wait a second.
That's what the respawn anchor is for.
It's to make it so that if I die I spawn here.
And not at the original spawn.
Right!
For a second before I was like wait a minute what was that then?
If it's not for the you know but that was the low stone.
Now I get it.
Maybe I really should do that now.
Just you know it's better for the future.
We've had so many freaking downs right now we need a W you know?
Can't even sprint anymore.
I guess just in time.
Oh!
Before anything else let me sleep here.
There we go.
So I forgot how this thing actually works.
What does it say in here?
Charge a respawn anchor to the maximum.
I have no idea how I did that.
I used to I did it once but I forgot how I did it.
I have no idea.
Oh!
Wait a second!
Right!
To make a low stone I need ancient debris!
That's why I can't make this yet.
That makes so much sense.
Right!
That explains it.
Wonderful.
I mean I don't even have any freaking armor.
Yeah and I don't have oh that's rough.
Am I really gonna make gold armor?
You're kidding me.
I mean at least we look stylish.
That's something.
Let's make a shield.
Oh my I can't believe I'm back here.
It's just unbelievable.
let's use this to make the tools.
So I need sticks
pickaxe and shovel.
I even lost my diamond sword.
And all my food!
Oh
my infinity bow is gone!
No!
What a tragedy.
Dude, should I?
Wait.
Yes.
Yes!
Yep!
We're bringing this.
It's only a little less armor.
That's fine.
At least we can't drown now.
In fact, why don't we crank this a little bit?
can we oh, can we put it like
where does the cranking go?
No?
Oh no, wait.
It needed a wheel that spins.
I do remember.
Let's see about the food.
I've got some bread.
I mean, it's better than nothing.
Yeah, today is self-improvement day.
we are gonna fix all the bad stuff in our lives today.
No more messing around.
I am tired of getting myself into situations where I'm just not ready for it, you know?
No more of that.
Sorry.
Oh, fuck.
I'm gonna charge this bastard.
Wait, uh, why do I never remember how this works?
this thing is such a mystery.
Like, why?
Is that a creeper?
I hear something moving in the in the undergrowth.
Is it, like...
Oh!
Give me that.
Oh, I thought it broke it.
Okay, good.
Dude, I ha...
How on earth do you...
I don't remember?
Like, why doesn't this work?
Is it here?
It literally will not fit.
I'm losing my mind.
Show me what's in here.
I don't...
I don't understand.
So, wait a minute.
Normally, I can...
I can attach the hand crank to this, right?
No, actually, I can't.
We have to connect it to a...
Wait, hold on a minute.
Oh, is it from the top?
Maybe it's from the top.
Do we have a...
We have one here.
You know what?
I'm going to...
do this real quick.
Oh, shit.
You know what?
Fuck it!
There's enough air in this anyway.
I...
Like, my brain is about to explode.
I can't deal with it.
Let's go get some food and find a whole new cave!
No longer the same cave.
New cave.
Completely new cave.
Yep.
Because I'm tired of this...
This cave over there is actually annoying me right now.
Such an annoying cave.
So I think I may have to slaughter some animals on the way.
So what I'll do is I'll take some coal with me and hopefully I have a smoker.
Oh
my...
Put this one in there.
We're going to smoke the meat when we find it.
What else do we need?
So we have food.
Torches.
Of course.
I know how to make those.
There we go.
Spyglass?
Tell me I have one.
I don't.
But it's easy to make.
Copper ingot and that thing.
Bop-bop.
Yes, dude!
I feel...
I feel complete again now.
This is so nice.
Now we need a bed.
Which I don't have, I don't think.
I think I have one over near the factory.
I'm going to go grab that.
And that...
Dude, I'm so ready.
I'm actually so hyped right now.
To finally fix my life.
In Minecraft.
You ever get those feelings and it's always like late at night?
Like an hour before bed where you suddenly get this burst of inspiration.
You know?
You're like, damn, I really should.
You know what?
From tomorrow, I'm going to eat better.
From tomorrow, I'm going to start exercising.
It's always in the evening.
That's how I feel right now.
And it's not even evening.
That's why it's so groundbreaking.
This means something.
Okay.
Let us head south and I mean really south.
And if I forgot something, I don't care.
We're going.
Operation Diamonds has begun.
I'm going to go way south to a whole new land.
In fact, I do think like the birch biome has a higher chance of spawning diamonds.
Don't quote me on that, but I just seem to have like memories of this.
But I do want to get a little...
Maybe it's the edge of this biome and then I go down or find a cave.
Okay, now I'm going to be happy if I find a cave.
And I'm going to kill you to get your meat.
So far, we have just gone south so it's easy to find our way home.
Hey, that looks kind of cool.
Doesn't it?
I'm not seeing a hole.
Maybe here.
I mean, we can breathe on the water.
Maybe we go down now.
Is this also the one that allows me to mine faster underwater?
I think...
No, that may be the boots.
The thing is, though, if we can connect to a proper cave from here, that would be nice.
So five minutes of breathing.
Actually, I don't want to be in the water.
I'm getting PTSD already.
I gotta get out.
I can just see it, you know?
I run out of the five minutes and then I die again.
The five minutes should be seen as, you know, backup time in case I find myself in the water anyway.
Not as a primary resource.
Okay, now show me a cave.
A nice, juicy cave.
Could be over there near the mountain.
Actually, I have a good feeling about it.
These cows shall die because I need food before I go in the cave.
You too.
Any more cows?
It's time to sleep.
Cheers.
I will reach credits today, by the way.
You may think it's going bad, and it is, but I'm still going to do it.
We will overcome.
Adapt.
Darwin.
Yi Ching.
Wait a second.
Where's north?
Where's the sun?
Oh.
Okay.
I think this may be a cave here.
Or not.
Kind of looks like a cave.
Maybe.
This could be it.
Oh yeah.
Here we go.
I'm not liking what I'm seeing, though.
Hey, bro.
I'm going to go this way.
How did you hit me?
I have my shield up.
Okay, this better be the biggest cache of diamonds of all time.
Or I will riot.
You could jump down there.
Bro!
We gotta go.
Ouch.
Dude, I'm dying!
Please, please, please.
I swear, if I die...
No.
Dude, I'm dead!
I'm fucking dead again!
Oh my god!
You take so much damage when you don't have diamond armor!
Christ!
Oh my god!
Smoke that meat!
Oh my god, there better be diamonds down here.
I will cause a ruckus, if not.
Let me see.
my life flash before my ice!
Nice.
Come on, hurry up!
There we go!
Moving.
Uh, we gotta go down to find diamonds.
Going this way.
I see you there, I see you there.
He's stuck, it seems.
It is so dark.
I don't like this cave, I hate these little, uh, stones.
Okay, there's lava though, that's always a good sign for diamonds.
Oh no!
Kill your friend!
Dude, I'm fighting for my life right now!
SHIT!
Oh my god!
I'll be good!
Fucking chill, game!
What the hell?
Fuck you!
My shield is gone!
I have no...
Dude, I'm so ready to start a new world.
I have no, I have no iron.
And there's, of course, no diamonds down here because, of course,
like, where the hell, here we go, are the diamonds?
Okay, well that's all I need right now.
Give me this.
I feel like the difficulty of the game has jumped a thousand percent since last time I played.
Like, I don't know how to explain this.
It doesn't make any sense.
In.
Uh, cook.
Then we can make a shield.
Just need one iron for that.
Here we go.
Man, that shield broke fast, huh?
That's messed up.
Like, way faster than usual.
This has to be, like, the worst cave of all time.
A million enemies.
No, no diamonds.
No drinks.
Can't do it.
Okay, you wanna dance?
Oh my...
He always gets in that hit every time.
There's nothing.
I'll take some, uh, more iron though.
We're also low on food.
You know what?
We're digging.
We're going down.
I am...
I am at a loss for what to do here.
I am just going down.
Good things happen when you dig in Minecraft.
An amazing cave is gonna open up.
And there's gonna be so many diamonds.
I'm gonna be swimming in them.
No, no, no.
There's really nothing here.
Not even sounds of animals.
Usually that's the indicator.
I heard something?
Make a sound.
Bro, I can't hear it through the music.
Uh, you know what?
My instinct tells me this way.
When in doubt, listen to your instinct.
You know what?
I actually kinda need this right now.
Just breaking blocks like this is kinda therapeutic.
After all that shit, this is exactly what a man needs.
Just making a tunnel.
It's like when you're a kid, you know, and you're frustrated.
You go into the yard and you dig a hole.
I used to do that.
Oh no.
No!
Not that!
Anything but that!
Okay, the other way.
Oh wait, I guess I...
Wait, hold on.
I can go swim.
I can breathe on the water.
We're gonna do this.
Yes!
Oh!
Diamonds!
I'm so glad I did this.
Yeah!
Okay, here we go.
It's looking up.
I don't like those spikes though.
I don't like that.
Let's just go the other way.
Maybe we can even find some...
Diamonds!
Yes!
Praise Jesus!
Or whatever they say.
Look at all this!
Oh, I'm glad I went swimming!
Oh, my luck is turning.
And now we're gonna go to the surface here and check it out.
In fact, we should make a pickaxe now.
Oh my god.
I did not expect to see all that lava up here.
Good news is, if I catch fire, I have water right next to me I can utilize.
Am I seeing any diamonds?
Hold on.
I feel like I need to increase my FOV here.
Feels a little cramped.
Okay, that feels better.
Slightly better.
Too much is also not good though.
Like, there's a sweet spot.
Fine.
Okay, let's make that pickaxe now.
Give me a moment.
Yes!
There we go.
Nine attack damage.
Okay, so that's actually the same damage.
Seven.
Should I...
You know what?
Let's just run with a sword.
I kind of forgot how that feels.
Maybe it's good.
I mean, the axe is kind of goaded, but...
We'll try the sword again.
Dude, there are just so many enemies.
It's insane.
Oh!
Ah!
We gotta conserve this food.
This food needs to last long enough to find enough diamonds to get a full suit of diamond.
And I am definitely getting lost here.
It is what it is.
I can't really change that.
I have no control over this.
I don't think I've ever seen so little diamonds in a Minecraft world as this one.
Like, the world has been stingy with it.
Ever since the beginning.
I've just not had any diamonds, you know?
Should I...
I'll grab some more of this.
Just in case we need an extra shield.
Now, that's more like it.
Look at this.
I see two diamonds already.
Three, actually.
Ooh, here we go.
Diamond biome, perhaps?
Oh, I see more.
I think...
No.
It's a fake diamond.
There we go.
The skeletons make me angry.
Like, it has just become personal lately with those skeletons.
More diamonds.
This is it.
We found the spot.
All our dreams will come true here.
Oh!
Look at that!
Interesting.
I'm definitely gonna go up there after exploring a little further.
No, I ran out of torches.
Oh,
I don't have enough wood.
This is really bad.
Oh, wait!
There's wood down here.
I'm saved.
We just found wood.
No problem.
Everything's cool.
More diamonds.
Dude, 14 already?
Very nice.
Man, this sword sucks.
That was like six hits.
I hear another spider.
Oh, it is so dark in here.
I need to...
Is the thing turned all the way up?
How do I change the...
Accessibility?
Brightness.
It is already max.
Damn.
Doesn't feel like...
It's maxed.
I think I'll go up to that mine.
Three hits with a sword.
Hold down.
Oh my god.
That got a little hairy.
Man, there's so many skeletons!
What the hell, man?
This ain't normal.
I'm getting my ass kicked here.
Did that guy just drop iron?
I've been imagining it.
I feel like I just saw some iron.
Weird.
Oh, diamonds!
Good shit.
And more...
Frickin' skeletons.
Come on.
You wanna fight?
Let's fight!
Okay, it's time to make some armor.
Nice.
Let's do legs.
That's it.
For now.
It's time to clean the inventory.
Ah, we don't need this, that, or...
This, that one.
Fuck these golden leggings.
And that one, this one, or that one.
We don't need this one anymore either.
I don't want leather.
Nope.
No gunpowder.
No bones.
Wonderful.
Good start!
We are way more armored now.
Things just got a lot safer.
We're not done.
We need full armor.
And then when we have that, full netherite armor.
I'm taking the digging machine into the nether, and we're gonna go crazy.
Wait, I wonder how that's gonna work.
So, is it just gonna dig through...
the netherites?
How would that work?
Also, it's not called...
It's called ancient debris.
I keep forgetting.
No, let's not risk it.
Look at this little asshole.
Oh yeah?
His hitbox is...
inconclusive.
That's the wrong word for that.
You know what I mean.
It'd make no sense, Captain.
I feel like I hit him.
I see you there.
Maybe that was it for the diamonds...
in this cave.
Last meet.
I mean, honestly, I just need one more...
diamond piece.
The other piece is gonna be...
gold, right?
For the nether.
So we don't need a full suit.
I really shouldn't be sprinting.
Get away from me.
God, you're annoying.
Okay, you wanna die?
Be my guest.
We've sucked this place dry.
There's no diamonds left.
Ah, here.
Oh, yeah.
I think...
Oh, nice, nice, nice.
I think I need like five...
pieces for the boots.
I think what a boot looks like.
And that's crafting thingy.
The shape of it.
Wait, I have a couple pork chops.
Let's cook those.
And then on this side...
What do we got?
Diamonds, come on.
Okay, five.
I need three more.
Wait a second.
I should have grabbed that...
Oh, I should have grabbed the wood while I was back there.
I don't have any wood now.
Misplay.
Oh, wow!
Look at this cave!
Have you ever seen anything like this?
That's crazy!
Wow!
That's kind of pretty.
I see diamonds.
Very cool.
I will grab that with pleasure.
We even have one of these things here.
But I don't really want that.
There's only one drug that will make me happy.
And its name starts with D.
What is that white stuff?
Wait, what the...
What the hell is that?
Is that snow?
Oh my god!
It's snow.
Interesting.
That is very unique.
I'm not seeing...
Oh!
Diamonds...
...have been spotted.
There's also an enderman.
Oh, here we go!
Oh, that's it!
Did that just light up?
Because I stepped on it.
Oh my god, there's more!
Massive deposit here.
Our luck is turning.
Wow, so many enemies.
It's a bit of a podcasting situation here, but, you know.
Such is the way of things when you don't have torches.
Maybe I can grab just a bit more.
Before I leave.
I saw something there, but that's gonna be a pain to get to.
Dude, maybe we just leave.
We got what we came for.
Let's not overdo it.
We don't have any, uh, torches anyway.
Like, we're done.
Get out.
You...
Okay, you really wanna fight me?
Now let's use up all these stray things here.
Gravel especially.
Podcasting, I can't even see on my own screen what's happening.
It is so dark.
I'm just hoping there's no lava up here.
And if there is, I'm gonna be fast.
I predict it's going to be...
4.51pm.
When we come out.
That's how safe I...
Uh, sure I am.
I heard lava.
I think there's lava next to me here.
It's gonna be a little problematic to get home, perhaps.
I think the best bet is just to go north.
Because at some point we'll hit the ocean and...
That should be the indicator.
So I don't actually think we're...
Destroy that!
I hate it!
I don't think we're that lost!
Like, it may feel bad, but, uh, it's not.
It's okay.
That just made me want to go pee.
When I get out and it's night, I'm gonna pee.
I wonder how common...
Like, what I'm doing right now.
Digging up and then doing this sort of, uh...
Thing.
I wonder how common that is for people to do.
Is that something that only I do?
Or maybe a bunch of people do this.
Maybe it's like the natural thing you do in Minecraft, you know?
It doesn't make sense, if you think about it.
To just get out fast.
And it's not really risky either, because if there's water up above, it's fine.
If it's lava, you can easily block it off.
I do understand digging down is a little risky.
But if you're fast enough, technically, it should be fine.
Then again, if you dig into a cave...
Then you can't even be fast enough with a block, so maybe it's not fine.
Yeah, actually, it's a bad idea, no matter what.
Okay, so it's water?
It's okay.
It's night!
I'm so good.
See, here's a problem.
I do not recall any snow anywhere next to my home.
Well, let's just go north.
This should bring us to the right spot.
Don't even...
See ya.
Good luck.
With one pork chop left, we made it out.
Eh!
Oh, I thought we were level 30.
But we're 20.
It's still good.
Yo, let's make a...
Oh my god.
I'm thinking of a digging machine that is on a huge scale in the net of now.
Not just a 3x3.
I'm talking something even more nuts than that.
Wait a minute.
I may be completely lost here.
We can't have gone that far.
Did I bring a bed?
I did.
I really should just sleep.
Sleep!
It's coming!
Can we make it?
Ah, you fucker!
Hate you!
Ruining my night's sleep.
Yeah, keep going north.
Trust in the north.
Guys, I think I'm finally recovering from the disaster start of the stream.
Like, I actually honestly think this start to the stream has been the lowest low I have ever had in Minecraft.
All the other stuff that I've experienced throughout time.
Maybe some of it comes close, but this is the lowest low.
Like, it just could not have gone worse.
It's a new record.
And I'm trying to think back on some of the worst times that I've had, you know?
In Minecraft, where things have gone wrong, and it's not even...
It's not even close.
Like, this was the definition of a shitshow.
You know?
Let me see.
I got ten diamonds on me.
Oh, that means I can probably make a helmet and some boots.
To be fair, though, maybe I should just make another pickaxe as a backup.
Oh, wait!
We can repair the other pickaxe we have!
The enchanted one.
We should totally do that.
Ah, but that one is, uh...
Ah, wait a second now.
That pickaxe is silk-touched.
Which is not great.
Yeah, I don't recognize this.
But it's good that we see these brown trees.
This is kind of promising.
That village says nothing to me.
I think we should get up high here and take a look around, because I think we may be closer than we think.
Maybe from this side over here.
Like, we may actually be already at the spot north.
We just have to go east or west, you know?
Probably east.
We didn't go that far in the cave, either.
Water that way.
Okay, I'm getting a little nervous now.
I ate all my food.
I thought I just witnessed a crime, but it's actually not a crime.
Let's get up here.
I need to look around.
I think we're actually kind of close.
Oh, yes!
Do you?
Yes!
I told you, man!
What did I say?
I said we were at the right spot north.
We just had to go east or west.
I could feel it in my bones, man!
God, I'm so good.
Like, the navigational skills in me have...
improved so much...
over the years in this game.
The only thing that's kind of...
that hasn't improved, and has actually...
you know, gotten worse...
is my combat capabilities.
But navigation...
I'm there, you know?
I got it.
We're gonna murder these cows!
Come here!
God, it feels good to be home with diamonds in hand.
Yeah!
Good night.
Dude, should we go kill the dragon?
With this?
Are we red?
No, we need a bow.
Need a bow for that.
Like, a decent bow.
We can't have a shitty bow.
We need a good bow.
The dragon...
Let's not underestimate the dragon, you know?
The dragon is actually difficult.
What if we employ the bet technique?
Dude, should we just go for it with the bet technique?
Wait a sec.
I need to practice.
I need to figure out how this works, actually.
I know how it works, I think.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
Let me see here.
Well, I would need bets.
Bets, bets, bets, bets.
I only have two wool.
Yikes.
And to make wool...
String.
Or...
The other thing.
Let me see here.
String.
No, it was...
Okay, yeah.
Whatever.
Okay, that...
It's not gonna happen, I guess.
Unless we find a village and we can, you know, rob them of some bets.
Wool is kinda hard to come by.
Uh...
Is it, though?
I have a shear.
And I have sheep.
So why don't we, uh...
Shear some...
Shear some sheep at the...
At the seashore.
That's all the sheep I have, huh?
Okay, okay.
Not bad.
Uh...
Oh, I see some more.
Don't leave!
I will murder you!
There we go.
Okay.
Close it!
Nice.
How many did I get?
Eleven?
That's like...
Three bets?
I have no idea how many I need.
In that speedrun video I watched, I think he used, like...
Ten bets or something?
I'm not entirely sure.
And I also gotta figure out how to do this without killing myself.
He was making some kind of, uh...
Thing, you know?
And then he did the thing up top.
Uh, let me see.
Stakes.
Rotten flesh is miscellaneous.
Let's make the diamond armor.
And I'm gonna say, let's make the boots.
Oh, that one only took four.
Okay, that's good to know.
And then we need a gold helmet.
Which I have.
Just like that.
Oh, good thing I looked at a shield.
We're gonna burn this in righteous fire.
And make a new one.
I even got some iron.
Let's blast the shit out of it.
Gunpowder.
That's miss.
Uh, I would say...
Yeah, flint is fine in there.
That's good.
Let's grab a little bit of this.
There we go.
Let's go multiply some sheep.
Uh, they wanted wheat, I believe.
Farming?
Yeah, wheat.
Uh, we don't have enough for the cows right now.
But that's okay.
They already have their skin back?
Oh my god!
I'm gonna skin them again immediately.
Oh, I accidentally fed a cow.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
Hold on.
Uh, wow.
So you can really get some wool fast here.
Show me the...
Where did I put that?
Shears.
Wait, this doesn't belong here.
Shears, shears, shears.
Oh.
Oh, I have them here.
Missed those.
It's so easy to miss things in your inventory in this game.
Dude, why is it growing so fast?
Wow.
Can I...
What about the small ones?
No, I can't do that.
Okay.
That's ten more.
Wonderful.
Dude, we're doing the bed technique.
Uh,
here.
So now we need wood.
I have it.
This may not be enough.
Uh, we gotta play this safe, dude.
Like, what if...
Oh my god, what if I can't...
What if...
Okay, hold on.
I'm imagining a nightmare scenario right now.
I'm imagining a scenario that would make me...
Skip straight to Doki Doki.
I'm not even kidding.
If I were to go in there...
Use my beds and be like...
Fuck yeah, it's working, here we go!
And then run out of beds.
And then we're stuck again and we have to kill ourselves.
That would be it.
I would not be able to handle that mentally.
We're gonna...
We're gonna get more beds.
It's already grown back!
What the fuck, bro?
Holy crap!
Come on.
Grow!
Grow, grow, grow.
Let me see those hairs growing!
I wanna see the hairs!
Show me that hair on your skin.
So I can chop it off.
Cause I'm him.
Maybe I go to bed.
Maybe that'll speed things up a little.
Get out of my way.
How many did I get?
Six.
Okay, nice.
Dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum-dum.
Would you like some dum-dums?
I really shouldn't, but...
I'll do it.
Two more.
That's only one more.
Oh, we need wood.
That's a lot of beds.
Hmm.
We also need something that does not get destroyed by an explosive.
An explosive?
Uh...
D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-dum.
Crying Obsidian.
I believe is the way to do it.
So, let me go in here.
We're gonna do a little experiment first.
Okay, so we're fighting the dragon now, right?
Uh...
Wait a minute.
How?
What if...
Oh, the dragon comes into the center, right?
Like it did last time.
So we wait for that.
And then we make...
Let me just grab some of this.
So...
Wait a second.
It needs to be...
Like up high, I guess?
Like this?
And then we do...
Wait, we may actually need more Obsidian.
Wait a sec.
I think we need more Obsidian.
Because it's gonna break...
You don't know what I'm talking about.
But I'm seeing it in my head.
You know?
And it's not working.
Okay.
This way.
Dude, I'm...
This is like the start of my speedrunning career.
This right here is the...
The budding beginning.
Humble beginnings of that.
Okay?
You'll see what I mean.
Uh...
I need more...
Obsidianos.
I'm gonna go grab some Obsidianos.
The bad news is...
I only have a shitty pickaxe.
And it's raining.
So I think...
I just need...
Two.
Let me actually grab a couple more...
Just for practice.
One more.
Okay.
So the idea is...
I'm gonna make a...
V shape.
Put the bed on it.
So that...
When it explodes...
It doesn't break horizontal or vertical.
Maybe I need...
Three actually.
Just to cover myself.
That's the one...
Big problem I have right now.
I don't know...
Uh...
How much damage I'm gonna take.
And how...
Yeah, I guess we're gonna experiment with that now.
Let's see.
Let's find out, shall we?
Okay, so this...
This is the center of the...
Of the arena, right?
This is how we're gonna do it.
We're gonna...
Remove this.
We're gonna do that.
This is what I'm envisioning.
Like that, right?
So...
So we sit down here.
Oh no.
Wait, what?
Oh, okay.
Okay, that works.
So...
Oh god, what if I die?
Wait a minute.
I need to sleep in my bed back home.
I need to...
What if I die?
We're playing this so...
Save!
Piss off.
I'm speedrunning.
Get out of my face.
Okay, I...
Imagine I die just...
Oh my god.
Like, it would be...
That would be a Doki Doki moment.
Right there.
That would be me switching over to Doki Doki.
If that had happened.
Um...
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
Sleep in the bed.
There we go.
Okay.
Now we're safe.
If I die, it's fine.
I mean, it's not fine.
Because we have a bunch of levels.
And you know, it would suck.
But whatever.
You know what?
Something tells me I need to make this higher.
But...
Let's see.
Do I stand here?
So as long as I'm...
Like, right barely touching...
Oh!
We took...
Jesus Christ!
I forgot about the fire.
There's fire, dude.
What the hell?
Put it out!
Dude, this dragon is gonna be my bitch.
I already have it.
Like, it's easy.
I got it, dude.
I'm ready.
That's all the practice I needed.
And you know what else?
We're gonna bring a fire protection potion.
Just because of this fire.
The fire scares me.
So we're gonna, you know...
Make sure that doesn't happen.
Thank you.
You know what?
We can't have a crime like this here.
It is crime land, but still.
Sorry, I just thought of a funny joke.
No, I didn't.
I got something in my throat.
Oh my god.
Why did I put rotten meat on the floor?
Five second rule.
The one thing I'm scared about right now...
Is that...
I'm not gonna be able to kill the dragon in time, you know?
Maybe this is not enough beds.
Let's go shear some sheep.
At the seashore.
Ah!
Sneep, sneak, sneak.
Nice.
Eight.
I believe that's two more beds.
Ah.
My god.
Okay.
Three obsidians.
And a bunch of netherrack.
Check.
Diamonds.
Uh...
Let's make...
Huh.
You know what?
I'm gonna bring one bow.
Just a...
With poison arrows.
Genius.
Just as a backup.
Just as backup.
Never know what's gonna happen.
Actually, I'm bringing a lot of arrows here.
Yeah.
I think we're ready.
Shield.
Did I not make...
It did.
Okay.
I think that's it.
Let me just double check here.
What else do I need?
I think I'm good.
Boat.
Ah, we need a bed.
I have a...
But I need to use these beds.
Oh, I have this bed.
Good.
The yellow bed is my sleeping bed.
The other ones are explodey beds.
Fuck me, dude.
Right in my home?
So rude.
Ah.
Okay.
So three obsidian.
We got the beds.
We got the bow.
Maybe a new axe, actually.
I don't trust like that.
Oh, I need sticks.
We don't like this.
Oh, food!
I need food, man.
Otherwise, we're not going anywhere.
Oh, imagine I go in there with no food.
I'm sorry.
You're all going to die now.
I don't care.
I know.
Nice knowing you.
I will take some sheep.
No, I leave the sheep here.
Yeah.
Eleven stakes.
That should be more than enough.
Yeah.
I think we're ready.
Like, I have everything I need.
I'm going to have twelve stakes.
We have the bow as a backup.
Uh, so I'm guessing...
The dragon's going to heal, right?
So, the way this strategy works, as far as I understand, is that you simply do so much damage that the dragon dies before it even gets to heal.
Right?
Yeah.
That makes sense.
We have the netherrack.
Wonderful.
This one can go here.
Oh, wait a minute.
Maybe I need some torches for something.
Yeah, let's just bring some torches.
You never know when you're going to need them, right?
Forty.
That's good.
The rest is looking nice.
Uh, this one should go...
maybe here.
There we go!
We're ready!
And I don't need no stinking eyes.
I remember exactly where it is.
Because, remember, I got the navigational skills of a master now.
Combat skills, not so much, but navigational.
Mm-mm.
So, as far as I remember, it's just northwest of here.
I'm trying to think what can go wrong.
I think I got it down, honestly.
And if the dragon is going to come to the center and sit there, I may not even need to make a, um...
like a tower.
I can just use the tower that's already there and put the obsidian on top.
That's how nice that is.
It's like it's made for it, you know?
Wait a second.
Isn't that already made of obsidian?
Ah, but it's good to bring some, I guess.
Just in case.
Wait, I don't remember being in this much wood.
Or maybe I do.
This should open up to, like, an ocean over there.
Should I?
Nah.
I didn't bring my smoker.
I could sleep in a second here as well.
Dude, the stronghold is actually sort of close to where I live.
It's kind of nice in that way.
Maybe I'll even make, like, when I finally get around to it, the trains.
A train that will take me directly to the stronghold.
Not only that, but it's gonna go across woodland areas.
It's gonna go across bridges on water.
We're gonna go down into a tunnel on the water.
To go down into this...
Oh my god, it's gonna be so, so nice.
I can't wait for that.
If, of course, everything is working as smoothly as I think it is.
When it comes to the trains.
Because I have an idea of how they may work, you know?
But I've never seen them in action yet.
So, that's it.
Now, the question now becomes where on earth...
I need my sumer.
We're not far off.
It's over there somewhere.
Should be here somewhere.
Maybe here?
That should be sort of obvious from
I may be in trouble.
Wait.
It's like over there.
You'll see.
I got this.
You know what?
Maybe it'll help if we go today.
Instead of running around at night, you know?
But...
Wait a minute.
I feel like I'm close here.
Maybe it's over here.
It was kind of far down, right?
Come on!
I know I'm close.
Uh...
Okay.
We gotta make a day.
I can't see shit during the night.
My phone is activating.
We're close.
It's like right here.
Let's see if this actually is way more visible during the day.
Oh yeah, it is.
It is, totally.
Very nice.
Now we should have no trouble.
Much better.
Uh...
I feel...
Okay, you know what?
It...
May be out here, actually.
Oh, dude!
I even remember now!
It's out here!
It's coming back to me.
Yeah, this thing...
Yes!
It's out here.
I think.
It should be sort of not too much of the green stuff.
It's like in a bit of a flat area on the ocean floor.
Man, last time I found it because there was stuff floating on the water, but that's not the case today, I don't think.
Oh, I can't see anything while in the water.
Don't do this to me.
This is too far down.
Do I admit the feet and go back for the ice?
Oh, man, no way.
But I...
No.
I had it, man.
It's over here.
Dude, I feel like it should be, like, right here.
I remember this land being super...
Like, it was somewhere right in between these lands.
I made a sort of, uh...
What do you call it?
A square in the water.
It's definitely not near all this green stuff.
Wait, is that it?
No.
I'm a genius!
Wait, what?
Did I?
I left two balls...
Oh, my God.
I'm double genius.
Yeah!
Hell yeah, dude.
Uh, I need, uh...
I need, uh...
More of this.
Gimme.
Go up.
Dude, I totally forgot about the boats.
Like, I seem to remember there were these, uh...
Ferns up here, you know?
Like, from the Galifianakis show.
But, uh...
This'll...
This'll do.
I'm happy.
Wait, I can't, uh...
Shit.
There we go.
Okay.
Now, this should be safe to go straight down, I believe?
Oh, God.
Please be right.
Why
was there one...
Wait.
That's...
Dude.
We're making a new world.
Why was there one block in between?
I made a...
How
does that make any fucking sense?
It doesn't make any sense.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe it.
Man, fuck this.
I feel like...
I need...
This is the worst stream I've ever done of Minecraft.
This is...
This takes the cake.
Like, this is just absolute dog shit.
It doesn't get worse than this.
This is my...
Like, remember when I said it was the lowest low?
It's way lower now.
Way down.
Dude, I was so...
Freak...
Like, I even thought about making a double hole to be safe, but then I remembered.
Oh, but it is fully filled.
Because I did that last time, and...
I don't know what I thought, man.
Like, why is that hole not filled?
I don't understand.
So, I was obviously digging down.
Right?
To get to the bottom last time.
But why was it then filled from the top?
Shouldn't have...
I don't understand.
Why was it not...
I don't get it.
Like, I'm trying to say it's not my fault.
It's not my fault.
It's actually not my fault.
I didn't do it.
It wasn't me.
Nope.
Oh, I don't want to make this boat again.
I'm tired of punching these trees and making a stupid-ass boat.
Fuck the Danish cows, bro.
I am so close to genocide right now on the cows.
This is pain.
Pure, unadulterated pain.
Dude, you know when you're, like, in this sort of state where you're sort of relaxing your eyes so much that it becomes all blurry?
Like, the vision is blurry?
And it's almost like it's more comfortable when you relax your eyes so they don't, you know, work overtime and it's all blurry?
That's how it is right now.
Like, I'm doing it right now.
The whole screen is, like, intermingling.
It's, like, blurry.
And I'm just in this state, you know, like, when I was trying to grab my item here, I was just sort of guesstimating because I'm, like, it's all blurry, you know?
I was like, where is it?
Is it down here or there?
That's what I'm going through right now.
You know what I mean?
Wait, I don't want to just...
Should I...
Stop breaking.
It's fine.
Man, I was peaking as well.
Like, it was...
Okay.
Here's the plan.
We're going to grab a bucket of water.
We're not going to give a shit.
We're not going to bring anything else.
We're going back there immediately.
And we're going down with a bucket of water.
Boom.
That's it.
We're not going to bring anything else.
I don't care.
Definitely no stinking eyes.
Nope.
I know the path.
I know the way.
It's just finding the boats.
And it should be easy because there's three boats now.
Oh God.
Don't FaceTime me.
Not right now.
I'm unavailable.
Don't do it.
Okay.
We're safe.
Ah.
Hey look!
TLT!
This is the worst stream I've ever done.
Like I'm legitimately I'm so sorry.
You know?
Like I get how fucking shit this is this stream has been utter shit.
Like I can't lie.
This is this is I'm sorry.
Oh this is the worst.
And you know what?
It's it's so embarrassing too.
We were gonna kill a dragon.
We're gonna kill the dragon.
Oh and then all this happened.
It's insane.
Like I better kill this dragon with the bed technique.
If we fail that it's Doki time.
Straight into Doki.
You best believe it.
I'm gonna I'm gonna go full with the voices and everything.
This is what's on the line guys.
It's either bedtime or Doki time.
Yeah.
Oh man.
You know what?
We're not even gonna go home.
We're going straight.
We're already on the water.
That's right.
No fear.
And you know what?
We don't need a bucket.
You know why?
Because there's water in the ocean.
And the water will naturally stream down now.
Think about it.
We're actually safe right now.
Hell yeah.
I nailed it.
That's it.
That's the solution.
And there's my lovely little windmill.
A sunset.
It's fine.
Don't need a bed right now.
Now the only problem right now is that I need to find my items sort of quick.
Otherwise they may disappear.
So as soon as I get there we gotta find those boats ASAP.
The good news is I know exactly where they are this time.
There's no mistake in it.
It's gonna be easy.
Oh wait wait.
I shouldn't sprint.
We are low on food.
Meaning we have no food.
Even if there's monsters we're not gonna sprint.
Who thought killing the dragon would be this difficult.
And I used to kill this dragon in my sleep.
And now look at me.
How do we get here?
You know like it's crazy.
It's on fire yo.
Everything is just messed up.
Otter Otter Punch
Oh my god.
That's horrible.
You know at times like this I resort to humor to get through the tough times.
You know it's a mechanism.
Survival mechanism if you will.
It works.
I recommend it.
And you know what I have to applaud myself here.
I feel like I have a resolve of steel right now.
After all of that you know it's gotta take something to keep going after that.
Ah yes music good that's what I need right now
the music of victory
we're close can you feel it it's bouncing around it's right in there and it feels good love the bounce okay so the ships or boats This... should be over... there.
Because we're not at the point yet with the islands and the stuff I talked about.
We're soon there.
In fact, I'm gonna line it up perfectly.
Right there.
The boats are gonna be exactly in this path.
Wait, I changed my mind.
This path.
Imagine if they are exactly on this path.
Are you imagining it?
Come on, come on.
Where art thou?
Oh, it's closed!
Look at that!
I nearly nailed it!
Wow!
Okay, we gotta go fast now?
No messing around.
We are on the timer.
And go!
There's no hole!
Punch it!
Fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Shit!
I gotta hurry!
Hold on, be right back.
This is so dumb.
Oh, no!
Dude, we're gonna be on the timer.
We're gonna lose it all.
Holy crap.
I cannot believe this.
I thought the hole was open.
Wait, how is the hole not open?
Didn't I open it just before when I died?
It doesn't make any sense.
X!
Go!
Oh, this gotta be close.
This gotta be close.
Now, this guy stole my boat.
That's fine, actually.
And...
Go!
And now we're going straight down.
Wait, uh, we're gonna catch our breath first?
Yes!
Okay, good.
The water's gonna stream down now while we catch our breath.
And go!
Oh, baby, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
My items, I see them, I see them, I see them!
Wait.
Fast!
Don't you die, motherfucker, don't you die!
Eat!
Oh my goodness!
You see that, Bradley?
Oh, wow.
Hold on, I need to eat a little bit more.
Why won't I go on a boat?
There we go.
Alright, go!
The bad technique is coming.
Oh, it's a coming.
Okay, good.
Uh...
We're gonna leave this water here!
I like this water.
Cheat!
No.
Wait, somehow all my items ended up in the right slots on my bar.
What the hell?
That's kinda crazy.
Okay, guys, I gotta take a piss real bad.
And there we go.
30 seconds.
We are back.
Here we go!
This is it.
The moment...
Is upon us.
Uh...
Okay, hold on.
On, on, on, on, on.
I guess the way we wanna do this...
We just wanna have as many beds here as possible so we can quickly grab them.
Maybe the food we keep.
Oh, god.
Okay.
Don't need the sword.
Don't need this.
Oh, I guess I can...
I can put it...
Uh...
Middle click.
And then destroy.
That's actually a better way of doing it.
Uh...
But I also need this.
I need this.
Uh...
Okay.
You ready?
Here we go!
The dragon shall die!
Ooh, yes.
Wait!
Items are in here!
Get the items!
Dude, those items...
I forgot about the items in here!
We gotta get them fast!
That's the first priority.
But we should be...
We should have plenty of time.
Yes!
Oh, my god.
This is massive.
Uh...
I don't need this, or that, or this.
What do I not need?
I don't need this.
What the fuck?
Leave me alone!
I don't...
I don't need this, or...
Uh...
This...
This one, this one...
This one...
Not this one, either.
Okay, go!
Go, go, go!
Grab the rest.
Yep, yep, yep!
Grab it, grab it, grab it!
Oh, yeah.
All these good things.
Very nice.
Eat the steak.
Oh, we also got extra steaks!
That's amazing!
Speedrun strats are coming!
Hold on.
Uh...
Get rid of this, and that, and this.
And this.
Uh...
Fuck the treasure map.
We don't need that right now.
Shield.
Uh, nice.
We have that.
Okay.
Uh...
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Get the beds!
No!
That's the...
Trash!
Beds.
What do I not need?
I don't know!
This!
It's down!
Hey, what's up, bitch?
Are you ready for some action?
Wait.
Uh...
Okay, so we wait now?
Watch.
We're gonna...
We're gonna bait him to shoot over here.
Oh, God.
I gotta be careful with these Endermen.
Uh, you know what?
I'm gonna make a...
Yeah, actually, hold on.
This is a great idea.
I'm gonna make a little preliminary, uh, EDP.
A PDP.
Just for when shit hits the fan.
Later on!
So I can run there.
Yep, that's good.
Also, I should probably have a weapon on me.
Get ready with the beds.
Let's...
Okay.
We can already put one.
So I guess I stand here and I go like this.
Come on, dude!
I wanna see you, uh, come here.
Come to me.
I'm scared of looking these guys in the eye.
I also don't want this, uh, particle stuff to be in the center right there.
That's gonna mess me up, I think.
I think it deals damage to me.
I forgot what it actually does.
Okay, it's gone now, good.
We're just gonna wait, we're gonna wait, we're gonna wait.
Come on, come on.
Are you coming or what?
Oh, okay, shooting that.
That's cool, that's cool, that's cool.
Come on.
I'm ready for...
Dude, I'm so excited.
Gotta be ready as soon as he's coming.
I'm just gonna walk around calmly here.
He's coming, he's coming!
Here we go, here we go, here we go!
Oh god!
I...
Oh sh...
Oh no!
No!
Oh, I'm...
I forgot the fire...
Protection potion!
How do I avoid this?
So wait, uh...
Let me stand...
Wait, I have an idea, I have an idea.
Here we go, here we go!
Oh no!
What's happening?
Why did I take so much damage?
Oh my god, I'm alive!
Dude, the bed technique sucks!
It doesn't work.
I don't...
I don't know what to do!
Uh...
Maybe we need...
Wait.
One more.
There we go.
Bro, this is the worst strategy of all time.
It...
We're gonna kill him.
We're gonna kill him the old way!
It ain't working.
Bad idea, bad idea.
We're gonna revert.
I got arrows.
We gotta destroy these crystals.
The beds are horrible.
Nobody likes it.
Terrible.
Oh!
The Enderman is taking damage from the little AoE.
Oh man.
Hey, I'm gonna have this.
In case I fall.
That's actually nice.
Oh fuck!
Wait, this one I could have just shot.
I thought this one was with the cage.
Damn.
Oh, don't walk into that.
Uh...
Give me my bow.
And put this...
Uh...
Yeah, it's fine.
Okay, just take it easy.
It's fine.
We're doing it the old way.
We don't need the bed.
Wonderful.
We're gonna shoot as many as we can.
Uh, maybe...
Honestly, maybe we just shoot, uh...
All the ones without the cage.
And then...
Oh my god, my aim is impeccable.
Watch this.
Oh!
Close!
Okay, that's a little...
Difficult.
Yeah!
Look at me go.
Did I hit that?
Oh my god, I hit it!
Amazing.
No, did I?
I don't know.
I got it!
Ha ha ha!
Wow.
I was so far away, you couldn't even hear the explosion.
Amazing.
Oh, that was close.
There it is.
Got it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's fine.
We may have to get up there...
...to grab that one.
Uh, there's also one...
Yeah, there's one up there.
I mean, is he really getting healed that much?
Maybe it's not too bad.
Wait, he's getting healed from this range?
Okay, well in that case, that is pretty bad.
Now we gotta go up here and fix it.
Let me also equip this just in case...
Oh, no.
That's all I need.
I need all these blocks.
Fuck!
Oh, god!
Oh, that was close!
Wow.
We're okay, though.
It's fine.
Got it!
Okay, so he's getting healed from that one now...
...and that one.
Oh, man.
We need more blocks.
Oh, my god.
We're gonna be such a high level when we beat the dragon.
I can't wait.
It's actually gonna change everything.
Our entire fortune is gonna be reversed.
You know, we're gonna have all the enchants.
It's gonna be amazing.
I can't wait.
Run, run, run, run, run, run.
Okay.
Dodge that.
Nice.
I actually just played safe.
Go over here.
I'm just...
I'm thinking about that sweet experience already.
Like, I can't wait.
Whoa, we just had an audio cut out there.
Game was lagging.
Okay, that's probably enough.
I think this one was one of them.
This one doesn't have a cage, but it's kind of hard to...
Come on.
Oh my god.
Destroy the middle one.
Good.
Back down.
Don't look at him.
Did I look at him?
I think we're good, man.
Man.
We're good, man.
Boom, baby.
Okay, this one on the tall tower, I can definitely hit from a distance.
Trust.
Oh, it's really tall.
That's gonna be...
Wait, I can't even see it.
Let me conserve my food.
I'm spending too much meat.
I gotta go really far away for this one.
Man, the bed technique is harder than I thought.
I'm gonna have to, uh...
come up with a better solution for that one.
Obviously, I'm doing something wrong there.
Wait, did I...
Or did I not remove the one up here?
Yeah, that's healing.
Oh my god, it's so close.
That's it.
What?
Oh my god, I'm being fucked by the RNG.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Did I get it?
That has to be it.
I think I got it.
Dude, I cannot even see it.
The tower is that tall.
Did I get it?
Oh, there's someone over here too.
And that's it, baby.
You're done.
Oh, crap.
Time to die.
That's right.
I'm coming for your ass.
Wow!
I've never seen that!
Dude just punched me!
Alright, alright, alright.
You wanna play like that, huh?
I'm gonna play like that.
I can play like that.
Can I return to center those?
Did I hit him?
There we go.
Wait, am I using poison?
Uh, use this here.
I think that's how you do that.
Okay, we need this guy to come to the center.
Right meow.
Oh my god, come on.
Is he being poisoned?
That's it.
You know what?
I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna axe him.
Hello, sir!
Don't mind me.
Oh.
Wow.
Didn't we have another guy on us?
Ah, that was close.
Okay, back.
Back to it.
I gotta conserve some arrows here.
I don't have infinite arrows.
What are you doing up there, sir?
That's gonna hit.
Nothing.
You know what?
Let me try the bed thing again.
Maybe the problem...
is that it was too high.
Just like that.
Watch this.
Here he comes!
Maybe.
Oh no, he's doing that crap.
He's putting particles on me?
What the hell is he doing?
We're gonna...
We're gonna bed him!
Here we go!
You ready?
I think we did it!
We hit him with it!
This is the strategy.
How do you not get hit by fire, though?
This is...
my problem.
You know what?
Let me prepare a double bed.
Oh yeah!
Double trouble.
Here we go!
Fuck you!
One more bed!
We're burning!
This is the worst bed technique of all time!
I don't know what I'm...
I feel like I'm doing it exactly as I saw in that video, but okay.
It has been like...
over a year ago since I saw that.
So, yeah.
Oh my god, I'm hitting all my arrows.
One more bed!
You know what?
It's getting a little risky with the bed.
Let's just, um...
Wait, it's bouncing off of him when he's doing that.
That's weird.
Let's just shoot him down, man.
I don't need no stinking beds.
Oh yeah!
So good.
Oh god.
That was not so good.
And...
Oh, he turned around.
He's flying through the...
Pillars?
Look at that!
He's bugging.
Bugging out.
With Q-tip.
Tribe Cult Quest.
Brother.
Do you mind coming down here?
I need to have a word with you.
Maybe you should prepare this fire situation for when he comes down.
Get ready with more beds.
Here we go!
Yeah!
I mean, it's doing good damage?
I feel like I'm kind of doing it.
What a shot.
Let's do it again.
I mean, I almost figured it out.
I just need to find a way not to get hit by fire.
I guess fire protection potion?
But there's got to be a way without that, right?
Okay, I'm just going to wait for him to come down here because this is...
How many arrows do I have left?
I have a bunch left.
Also, I'm not really using these poison arrows.
Do they need to be, like, first?
I keep forgetting the order here.
Yeah, so now I'm shooting them.
Okay, good.
Oh my god.
Will you please just...
Here we go!
Boom!
Suck on that one.
I mean, it's just a matter of time.
I got them.
Not even close.
And now we're poisoning him.
Although it doesn't look like he's losing HP from that.
Coming back.
I think he's angry.
Oh god!
Wait, he poisoned me?
What the hell?
He's got poison breath.
Insane.
Wow.
Wait, is there an Enderman on me?
No, that's not.
Okay.
Good night!
Beautiful!
That's amazing.
Look at all this experience.
Oh my god!
That's a lot!
Oh!
Holy crap!
Okay.
So wait, how do we respawn the dragon?
Hold on.
I'm not gonna fuck it up this time.
Let me see here.
Adventure.
Oh, it's probably the end.
Let's see here.
Yeah, okay.
So we need these.
Dude, I don't remember what I have to do.
I have to do something.
And I think it was something to do with the egg.
The reason I couldn't do it last time is because my egg was just gone.
Like, off the face of the earth.
Oh wait, it's up there.
Huh, interesting.
You know what?
I'm gonna leave it here for now so I don't, you know, get it lost again.
Now I know where it is at least.
Level 64.
I will jump into this.
And would you look at that.
I told you I would get credits today.
Didn't I?
We're not gonna watch it though.
Because come on.
Okay, uh, nice.
Now we leave.
And the good news is we have an elevator.
Oh wait, uh, we can do that down here.
Dim, dum.
Oh, I like this song so much.
It's perfect right now.
Yes!
Fuck these little guys.
I don't care.
Let me up.
Dum, dum.
Bum, bum.
Gula, la, la.
Oh, come on.
Fuck, let me in.
Let me in!
Why is this so hard?
Yeah!
Go!
Go to freedom!
We have done it.
We have defeated the dragon.
Dum, dum.
Beautiful!
And look at all these ships we have here.
Amazing.
Hold on.
This way.
I mean, I knew that.
I just wanted to confirm.
We even got everything back.
We got the toolboxes back.
We are so back, baby.
Level 64!
We're gonna be enchanting.
It's gonna be so good.
We may need more bookcases, though.
Man.
Bookcases.
Dum, dum.
Cheers to that one.
I can't believe it.
We actually made it.
Man, after all that heartbreak, this was so cathartic.
Fantastic.
I feel so good now.
Like, everything went to shit and now I'm like on cloud nine.
The worst thing that could happen right now is that a creeper spawns out of thin air falls on my boat and kills me.
If that happens, I don't know what I would do.
Run down the street naked.
Probably.
Lathered in oil.
And I would flop around like a seal, you know?
Making noises.
As a sort of, uh...
protest.
Against everything.
Something like that, at least.
I probably wouldn't do that, but I would think about doing that.
I'm just happy.
No matter what, I cannot call this one a failure.
We came out on top.
What a beautiful day it is.
Look at that.
The sun is shining.
The cows are mooing.
The bees are whispering.
Wait, if cows moo, what do bees do?
Think about it.
Nobody has ever asked these fundamental questions before.
But I feel like it's essential that we get to the bottom of it.
Right?
I don't think humanity has an answer to this.
This needs to be investigated.
By top people.
There's probably top people on this as we speak.
I always love that expression, you know?
We've got top people working on it.
Like, who are these top people?
Do they introduce themselves as a top person?
When you talk to them, or what?
So weird.
It's like the fox.
What does the fox say?
I mean, I'm not trying to reference that song.
I mean, obviously, that's, you know, a thing, but...
There's no word for the fox.
There isn't.
The fox is in the bees.
Where's my boat?
There it is.
It wouldn't surprise me if that noise was also made by a human.
That's not a real sheep.
That's Notch making that noise.
I know it is.
That's something a Swedish person would do.
I just know it.
Classic Swedish person behavior.
Also, am I actually already on the right island?
I got a little disoriented on my way here.
because I was so happy.
I didn't pay attention.
No, I think I had to go in the water once more.
Yep.
I remember this spot here.
We had a forest fire that we tried to take out, remember?
Successfully, I might add.
Although it wasn't easy.
Fire.
It turns out it's spreading fast.
When there's flammable materials around.
By the way, isn't it soon...
Wait a minute.
It's Halloween soon.
Isn't it?
When is Halloween?
It's October.
I think.
September, October, November.
Yeah.
It's gotta be October.
I was just thinking about that when I saw those mushrooms on the way here.
No.
Orange rooms.
You know what I mean.
The orange things, man.
The ones you chop and cut to make faces out of.
I think this year I may actually do that in real life, you know?
I used to do that with my ex, but I kinda stopped doing it when I broke up with her.
But maybe I'll do it this time around by myself.
I'm just gonna sit next to Jackie and we're gonna cut faces into, uh...
orange rooms.
I need to repair this one.
Is it worth it, though?
Hold on.
Efficiency 3 is kinda bad anyway.
Dude, we make a new one.
Let's see what we can make.
Not that one.
Okay!
I don't mind that!
That's pretty good.
Fortune 2.
Hold on a second.
Also, um...
I need more bookcases.
And I do have lots of books.
Look at that.
And beef.
Let's cook it.
I'm so excited.
We're gonna...
Oh, we cannot blast it, but we can definitely smoke it.
We also have a...
Oh, man.
Our original armor is back.
Oh, it's fantastic.
That's so nice.
This one is back, too.
Uh...
Shovel is back.
This one goes in here.
All these arrows, we don't really need them right now.
Or this one.
Do need that one.
Ah, I need to make a good bow, too.
What I have right now is not enough.
Oh, by the way, uh...
One of the reasons I wanted to go there was to find new materials like the endstone to see if we could make new stuff out of it.
Um...
But I didn't really focus on that this time around.
I'll probably go back and grab all kinds of stuff.
Especially from uh...
The end where you find those cities, right?
I wanna grab all this...
Like, uh...
Shulkers and all that.
No, not Shulker.
Oh, what's the word?
Is it...
No, Skulk?
I forgot which one is which.
But you know the ones where you can make the little spinny chests?
That's...
That's what I want.
That material is what I want.
I want it.
Oaks!
Uh, we also don't need an extra shield.
In fact, get the shield off of me.
Its shadow is blocking my toilet.
I have two spy glasses.
Uh...
Right.
I wanted to make bookcases.
Let's do it.
Or, I guess, bookshelves.
Five of them?
Don't mind if I do.
Deep.
I mean, I like fortune too.
I do.
But, uh...
Hmm.
Let's see what else we can do before we do anything.
Maybe there's a better bow.
Always check everything, right?
Unbreaking?
I don't really care.
That one is not exciting.
Uh, let's check all these.
Uh, wait a minute.
Helmets, chestplate, and legs.
They all share the same one, right?
Right?
No, wait.
It can't.
Thorns, respiration, and...
Okay, so they are different.
Never mind.
I was misinformed.
Uh, let's use a sword.
Fire aspect.
Wait, is that the one that cooks my food?
Because in that case, I want this.
I'm gonna take this.
I'm taking that.
Definitely want fire aspect.
That's amazing!
Smite four?
Yes, sir!
I'll take that.
And silk touch is not bad either, but we already have a silk touch pickaxe.
So maybe not that exciting.
Fire protection is pretty good.
Protection four is pretty good, but we need a fresh set of armor for that.
And I don't have it.
I can maybe make it.
I cannot!
Damn.
Okay.
Uh, what about axe?
Oops.
Let's see here.
Let's actually make a new axe.
For that, I need some of this.
Maybe another pickaxe too.
Oh, I gotta check the bow as well.
Flame!
I mean, that's not bad.
We can give it a whirl.
But, wait a sec.
I feel like I should almost go for this.
Because it's not that common, you know?
Like, it is kind of rare to get this.
And it's not fully repaired, but that's fine.
Okay, it's just hook touch.
That's unfortunate.
Unbreaking 3 is actually not too bad.
Yeah!
That's what I'm talking about, baby!
Oh, yeah.
And the best part is...
Ah, I thought we could combine these two, but we can't.
I need to make a new bow.
Because I want power 5, baby!
Unbreaking 3...
Okay, efficiency 3 is decent.
I think I'm gonna go for that one.
Nice!
Which means we can combine these two to make efficiency 4.
And I'm doing that right now.
No, wait!
We shouldn't do that yet.
We do that when we have under 30 experience.
That's when we do it.
Let's see here.
Infinity is pretty good.
Maybe I should go for that.
Then again.
I wonder if Infinity is compatible with power.
Let me check.
Power?
Ah, but wait!
I need to make Infinity first before I can check that.
But, like, this one is amazing.
You know?
Obviously, we're gonna do this, but not yet.
What about the old axe?
Axe, axe, axe.
Oh, wait!
Not this one.
We gotta check the other one.
Okay!
I mean, that's not too bad.
Unbreaking 3.
Should I?
Let me check what else I can get.
Aqua Affinity.
Unbreaking
I need to make another bow.
Currently, I have power 4.
I'm gonna...
Yeah, I'm gonna do this.
Okay.
Nice.
Unbreaking on that.
We're gonna get Unbreaking 4 with these.
Let's see if they're actually compatible with Infinity.
Oh, they are!
Oh my god!
It's amazing!
Okay, so this one is cheaper.
I still don't understand why that is the case.
Like, when you switch these around, sometimes it's just cheaper.
Also, it doesn't look like I can get higher than Unbreaking 3.
Right, okay.
So that was the max.
Got it.
Although...
Hmm.
I'm trying to think.
Maybe I should wait until I have a power 4 bow again so I can combine them to make power 5?
But having Infinity is very nice.
Nice.
Definitely a waste to do it now because, you know, level 49 so let's not do it yet.
Let's check the Pickaxe situation.
Do I even have any left that can be enchanted?
I may not.
Wait, Efficiency 4 on this one.
Efficiency 4?
3.
Oh!
These two can be combined.
Let's just, uh, you know, arrange them like this.
These two get combined.
Let's check the armor.
Protection.
I want Protection 4.
Then I'm all in.
Only 3.
Shovel is unbreaking.
Man, this sword is incredible!
Very nice sword.
Honestly, I'm not too...
Mmm...
I really wish I could make another Pickaxe here.
I just don't have enough Diamonds.
Ah, it hurts.
I feel like we should go get more Diamonds just to have more Pickaxes.
You know?
Or make another bow.
Actually, let's do that.
Another bow would be nice.
Let's see what we got.
Power 4 would be King.
Yeah!
I'm taking that.
Woo!
Wait, Flame?
Wait a second.
What's the...
Flame?
Dude, I want to combine all these three bows.
This is going to be a Master Bow.
Wow.
Okay, that's not interesting.
Unbreaking.
Also, I don't have any boots.
Oh, wait.
I don't even have any...
I do have.
Death Strider.
I don't think that's very interesting.
What about my Protection 4?
Can I not get that?
Hello?
I'm breaking 3.
What else can I enchant?
Let me think.
Oh!
Let's enchant a Fishing Rod.
Let's have a look there, shall we?
Lure 2.
Don't think that's very interesting.
That's one of the bad ones.
Like, I want Lure 3 or 4.
So wait.
Silk Touch Efficiency 4.
These two together make Efficiency 4.
And then these two together with that one Efficiency 5.
That's gonna be an ultimate Silk Touch Pickaxe.
If you think about it.
That's not bad.
Oh!
Wait a sec!
Can I enchant this?
No way!
Okay!
That's pretty cool, but I don't want Thorns.
I want to make a new diving helmet.
Glass and copper ingot.
Okay.
Oh!
Wait!
Isn't that like perfect?
For a diving helmet?
We gotta go with that.
Oh!
That's a good one!
Wow!
Very nice!
Let's see this one now.
Capacity!
That's a new one!
Wait, there's new enchantments!
We gotta go for this.
Fire Protection!
But that's kinda useless on the water, I guess.
Whatever.
I'll take it.
Let's check the Fishing Rod.
Lure 2 again.
All righty.
Bow is punched too.
Oh, that's gonna punch them backwards.
Oh, look at the bar!
It went down a bit, so yeah, capacity just means there's more room in here.
Efficiency 4 on an axe.
That is very, very nice.
I think I'll take that.
Oh my god!
Yes!
One...
Dude, I'm getting all the crazy enchantments here.
Unbreaking 3.
Where's my Protection 4?
Hello?
Should I just go with Protection 3?
I feel like that's not good enough.
Right?
Maybe you cannot get higher than Protection 3 from enchanting at the table.
Wow.
Hmm.
Wait!
Can I enchant this?
No, okay.
Haha.
What about these?
No?
I mean, at this point, you know, gotta experiment.
Unbreaking 3?
Guys, I'm gonna get a lure 3 from this.
Oh!
That's not bad either, though.
I'll take it!
Haha!
Very nice.
Now we're at 34?
Uh...
Okay.
Power 4 on a bow!
I feel like we gotta just make a new bow with that.
Like, that would be a waste not to do.
What about hos?
Can we get some of those?
Unbreaking...
No, that's boring.
We don't want unbreaking.
Oh god, what else can I...
Like...
Okay, so there's obviously new enchants.
Maybe we can enchant a shield?
With create?
No.
Uh, what about the copper diving boot thingies?
Yes!
Let's try these.
Surely something's gonna happen there.
What's up with the fire protection on the diving stuff?
Hello?
Nobody needs that.
Useless.
Can we stop with that?
Maybe another fishing rod?
And then we combine the lures to get an even higher lure?
Oh wait, not fire.
Fish.
I keep thinking of fire when I think of water now.
Uh, right.
Oh, we need more string.
I don't have it!
But I have it.
But I don't have it!
Because it's not active.
Uh.
But we can crank it!
We can crank it.
I'll take it.
No, I don't want to do that!
I hit it.
Uh, put it back.
Can I do it manually?
I can't do it manually.
God!
Uh, this goes in here.
I don't know what to enchant.
I need to enchant something.
Uh, maybe...
Maybe we do another sword?
I don't have enough though.
There we go!
Protection 4!
Let's do it!
Very nice.
Okay, now we're at 31.
Yes!
I need more blue.
Oh, you can't tell me we don't have more blue.
No way.
Wait, what's it called?
Lobby's Lazuli.
No way.
No!
Maybe over here.
Oh, man.
What a buzzkill.
Wait, that's what bees do.
They buzz.
Right.
That makes sense.
Wait a minute.
Maybe there is a word for foxes.
Hmm.
I don't know.
Anyway.
Let's, uh, let's go find some blue.
Dude, I...
This is, like, killing the dragon?
I feel like that's gotta be one of the first things you do in a world.
It is just so incredibly helpful when it comes to...
I mean...
Okay, first of all, you gotta get the enchanting table.
And after that, dragon.
It's not even that hard, you know?
It's nice.
All right.
Let's put in the stuff.
Oh, you know what?
Actually, I'm gonna use these, uh, levels now to combine.
I'll say fuck it.
Power four.
So that's gonna cost eleven.
Fifteen.
Hmm.
What would be cheaper?
I think it may be better to do this first.
No, wait, wait.
These two first.
Eleven.
And then this one.
Now that is a god bow.
Sixteen, though.
Okay, you know what?
I'll do the, uh, pickaxes instead then now.
That's gonna be...
So these two, it's gonna be efficiency four, and then together with that it's efficiency five.
Only four!
Nice!
Huge.
And then these two.
Okay, fourteen either way.
Silk Touch, efficiency five, unbreaking three.
That is chef's kiss.
Wait.
Yeah.
Yep, that's good.
That's good, man.
Very nice.
I would love not to have Silk Touch on it, though, to be completely honest.
Maybe I shouldn't have put Silk Touch on that.
That's kind of annoying now.
I need another pickaxe that is non-Silk Touch.
Yeah.
Ah, shit.
That's fine.
Put on some boots, man.
Level two.
We actually used up, like, 65 levels just now.
Wow.
Very cool.
And I feel so much better.
This is incredible.
Now, I'll be running around with this bow.
because it's so nice.
That means we need arrows.
That was hard to say.
You go in there.
Curse of Vanishing.
I feel like I just want to destroy this.
Let's, uh, disenchant it.
Wait, where do I do that?
This, uh...
I think it's this one.
No, wait.
Disenchanting.
I do not remember.
Why the hell?
Yeah, I don't know.
It's somewhere.
I don't think I can make that yet.
Yeah.
This is my...
Ah, but I don't want to carry this around.
Silk Touch sucks ass.
God, I...
Oh.
I regret making a Silk Touch.
Can I, like, selectively remove that?
Is that somehow?
That's too bad.
In any case, we need more diamonds.
And let's just have a look.
See if we unlock something new today.
Snow?
Oh.
Weird.
Redstone Requester.
But that's not new.
I guess we made this last time and we didn't look at this yet.
That's kind of intriguing, though.
Redstone Requester.
Wait, what?
Oh, Trap Chest.
And the Redstone Lamp.
Waxed Cover Bulb.
Okay.
Let me see here.
Anything new in here?
Cracked Pal...
So long names.
Okay.
I guess not.
Sugar.
Do I actually get more sugar out of this than normal?
I guess this one is extra.
Right?
Mixing.
Sugar, cocoa beans, milk.
Makes sense.
Dude, should we make, like, a Willy Wonka's Chocolate Factory?
You know?
I feel like we could do that.
Just make so much chocolate.
We're gonna drown in it.
I wonder if you can make a lake of chocolate and then drown mobs in it.
Wouldn't that be cool?
Like a giant witch's brew.
And we're gonna add mobs' ingredients.
That sounds fun.
Yeah, so you just...
You just take the chocolate and you press it.
Or you compact it and then you get a bar.
Makes sense.
Aviator's Goggles.
Just leather to that, huh?
Augments your hut with miscellaneous information about place components.
Kinetic components show added stress.
Okay, so that's just, like, the normal goggles.
Some other blocks reveal information such as item and fluid content.
So what is the exact difference?
It's the exact same.
This one adds armor, though.
So it's a little better.
Tiny bit better.
Why not make it?
Who knows what it'll unlock.
Maybe something new.
I must have some...
leather.
There we go.
Oh, wait.
I remember.
So it's just...
Goggles with leather.
Aviator's Goggles.
High Fashioned.
That's an achievement.
Dude, that actually looks kind of dope.
Now the question is, of course, can that be enchanted?
No.
It cannot.
But maybe the normal goggles can be.
I didn't check it.
But it is possible.
These are just better goggles.
Let's actually put that in there, too.
Yep.
I probably should be wearing this.
And I'm not going to the...
Ah, but wait a minute.
I am going to the nether.
That's the next step.
We're going to the nether.
I'm actually going to make a new helmet, because this one is about to die.
I will burn the old one.
I almost burned my ingots.
I have definitely made some mistakes in the past by throwing stuff into lava.
I'm going to be extra careful with that.
From now on.
We cannot take any risks.
Wait.
Did I just fucking burn the wrong helmet?
Whoops.
That was a mistake.
That's fucking hilarious.
I can't believe I did that.
I was like, wait a minute.
Where did my helmet go?
Oh, no.
Okay.
There we go.
Dude, I'm so ready for the nether.
The first thing we're going to make is a...
Ah, but wait a sec.
Netherite pickaxe.
I think the way that works, if we have a good diamond pickaxe, we can convert that into a netherite pickaxe, and it has all the same stats.
So I think we're chilling when it comes to that.
Don't need a bucket for the nether, for obvious reasons.
Do need some extra wood.
But this ain't enough, Captain.
We need at least 24.
Uh-huh.
And...
Efficient's the four axe.
Definitely bring in that instead of this.
This is all good.
Yep.
Now, food is the big problem right now.
I need a better food supply situation.
So I think...
Actually, before I go to the nether, we're going to have to make a little list here.
Before going...
To nether...
To find netherite...
We shall...
Create an automated...
Um...
Cow killing...
Device.
Maybe even an automatic cow killing device that deposits the meat...
Into a...
Blast fan...
No.
A smoking fan.
And then outputs it...
Via filter to a chest.
So we have automatic meat coming in.
That's it.
That's the next step.
In fact, I'm going to open this...
And quit.
That's it.
We have done it.
I will say...
Let's actually not...
With this one.
Let me switch it over.
What a disaster of a stream.
I apologize, man.
That was a shit show.
I was going to say from start to finish, but towards the end, we kind of managed to redeem ourselves a little.
It started out so...
I was so close to starting a new world.
I'm not even kidding.
Like, out of frustration.
What a terrible start.
What a terrible start, man.
Like, I couldn't have done anything else at the start, right?
Other than punching blocks.
And that's not even going to work.
There is no way I could have defeated that dragon.
Actually, there is one way.
If I had killed the crystals that were not in cages, and then somehow done more DPS than the healing, then maybe.
But other than that, you know.
Next time, it's going to be Doki Doki.
Yes.
We're probably going to finish it next time.
But who knows?
Maybe it's going to be two more streams.
We'll see.
Amazing speed running.
Thank you.
I tried my best with the pet technique.
Will you ever try RimWorld?
I have actually tried it before.
I tried to play it a little.
Many years ago.
It seemed fun, but it was kind of overwhelming.
I didn't really understand what was happening.
And I played maybe three hours.
Barely remember anything.
But I do want to play it again.
Because I remember the music being so good.
And the vibes were immaculate.
So...
Yeah.
We're going to play that at some point.
And it's so much more overwhelming now.
Really?
Have they done a lot of updates to it?
I thought even at that point, the game was already...
You know...
Polished and updated as much as possible.
The best strat was so scuffed.
I know.
It was so bad.
Like, I'm definitely doing something wrong.
Like, I think...
Towards the end, I sort of had a strategy going.
But...
The problem with that one was that I got hit by the fire.
So maybe the solution is to...
I'm not actually sure.
Maybe I also elevate myself a little to get off the ground.
Maybe the fire only hits the...
I don't know.
We'll have to experiment with that.
I was talking about Rimworld just now.
Because someone asked about it.
Ellipse V.
Yeah, the dragon was breaking some of the beds.
Because I think the bed was too high.
You know?
So when the dragon hitbox is...
Flying into the bed, it actually breaks the bed.
So that's why I did it a little further down in the end there.
And it seemed to work.
The dragon, yeah.
Is there...
Wait, is there a lunar eclipse tonight?
There's not.
Again?
You're kidding.
Hold on.
Really?
No fucking way.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, right, right, right, right, right, right.
For some reason, I read it as solar eclipse.
I was about to say that.
That's crazy.
I see now.
Okay, yeah.
My bad.
I misread that.
It's because I had the solar eclipse on my brain lately.
Maybe I'll look at it, though, the blood moon.
The bed technique is harder than it looks.
It definitely is, dude.
I was so convinced I was gonna do it, like, first time.
After that first attempt in the nether, where I just tried it on my own as practice, I was like, I got this.
Easy.
You know?
And funny thing is, when I did that in the nether, I didn't get hit by the fire.
Yes, the fire spread all around me, but I didn't get hit by it, you know?
Because I was standing right beneath the bed, so maybe that was the reason.
I don't know.
But it's kind of difficult, yeah.
I did not play Doki Doki today, but next time I stream, I'm gonna play Doki Doki.
I've not tried snooze.
I don't smoke.
I don't do any of that.
13th episode, blood moon coming.
Today is a dangerous day.
That's one way of looking at it.
It would be the cherry on top if it was Friday, too, but it's not.
It's Thursday.
It's a little Friday.
So, you know, it's a little Friday the 13th.
I did try shaders in season...
Towards the end of season 1 and also some of season 2.
I mean, they're nice, but in the end, I gravitate towards non-shaders.
I just like the default look.
It's a vibe.
Did you hear about Tim Curry?
I feel like I've heard that name before, but I don't know who he is.
Tim Curry.
Oh, it's the actor!
What happened with him?
Oh, did he die?
Oh, that's sad.
I always thought he was hilarious.
I like Tim Curry.
Yes, I have tried shaders, Bashti.
But I prefer the vanilla look of the game.
But the shaders look nice.
I mean, I'll say that.
Sometimes it's nice to play with it, you know.
But for extended periods, I do just like the default look more.
But apparently...
Oh god, what are they called?
Mojang.
Or Mo...
Mojang?
I keep forgetting how to say it.
They are adding shaders to the base game.
Also, when is that coming?
I feel like that news has been in the works for like over a year.
When is it happening?
When is the official shader thing coming?
I feel like they're so slow with development.
Like, am I crazy?
Such a big company and it's like...
When is this shit coming?
What the hell are they doing?
It's only on Bedrock for now.
But they were promising...
That also...
On Java, right?
I read that.
Like, over a year ago.
That's the crazy thing.
Like, modders just make it...
You know?
Like, how can I...
I don't know.
I don't know, man.
They're just so slow.
It's crazy.
They're reworking the graphics engine for Java as we speak.
I mean, yeah, okay, but...
They just have such a big team, don't they?
Like, it's a big company.
Well funded and all that.
Maybe it's a talent thing.
Maybe they just don't have that much talent working there.
I don't know.
It seems insane.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe it's like a very small team.
At least two guys.
I think you're right.
Make an airship next time.
Maybe I will.
Nah, probably not.
Right now I'm focusing on trains.
That is like my immediate goal, you know?
But I keep getting distracted by other things.
Because I don't have what I need to make the trains yet.
So I'm trying to figure that out, of course.
We're not going to play Doki today, but next time.
Isn't it like the bigger the team, the slower the development?
That entirely depends on the team.
I mean, obviously you can't make GTA 6 with five people, right?
That's going to take literally a hundred years.
So there's a sweet spot, you know?
If it's too big, yes, it's going to get bogged down by...
What's it called?
Like management stuff and...
It's like bottlenecks all over, you know?
It's going to be a problem.
So there's a sweet spot, I guess.
Next stream is day after tomorrow.
I'm like 99% sure.
So that would be on Saturday.
The next Minecraft update is amazing.
Okay.
Looking forward to it.
I have not played GTA 4!
That's the one Grand Theft Auto I have not played.
I did install it on PC back when it came out.
But that game ran like ass!
Like it was terrible on PC when it launched.
And I also didn't have a very good computer, so I just didn't play it.
Yes, I've played GTA 6.
I got early access.
I think I'm like 30% through it at this point.
I bet it also had some crackling in the background, am I right?
I don't remember.
Could be.
Didn't even know there was a remaster, Frank.
But I did hear that some modders made the game pretty well optimized.
And, you know, implemented some graphic stuff and all that.
So it's apparently really good with that mod.
I saw it on Digital Foundry.
Is there sex too?
I heard that's coming next year.
Modders are the best devs.
Yeah, there's definitely a correlation there, right?
If people make something because they enjoy it so much, it's usually going to be a good product, right?
Compare that to a company where...
And it's not always the case, of course.
But some companies where the people working there don't even like the product they're working on, obviously they're not going to give it their best.
That's just a fact.
So it's not going to be as good.
But I don't know when Mewgenics is coming.
When I feel like playing it, and it's, you know...
I know it's not much of an answer, but...
I guess the answer is I don't know.
I mean, it's not going to be in the next month.
And it's also not going to be in 10 years, you know?
So somewhere in between.
But probably a year?
I don't know.
Something like that.
XCOM with cats.
What is not to love?
Dude, I heard they were making this Star Wars game that is like XCOM.
But I feel like I should play XCOM 2 before that.
I mean, I said not in 10 years.
Definitely not in 10 years.
I mean, definitely within 100 years.
I can almost guarantee it.
Isaac is over, yeah.
At least for now.
Maybe I'll get the urge to jump back in at some point, but...
Historically speaking, that's probably not going to happen.
Maybe if an update comes and I just have the urge to, you know, play some roguelike, maybe.
But then again, if roguelike is something I crave, probably the next roguelike I play, it's going to be Hades 2.
You know, I can just see myself in that situation.
If I have the choice between the two games, I'm going to go with Hades 2, right?
Yeah, with the spooky month, hmm.
I do want to play something spooky.
I just haven't decided what it is yet.
Maybe the little...
What's it called?
Little Villagers?
Or what was it?
Something little, little.
And it's like a horror game.
Yes, Little Nightmares.
Thank you.
Little Nightmares or maybe Alien Isolation.
Or what are those games called?
There's like two of them.
Where you have like a camcorder and it's like first person.
God, what is the name?
It's something that a lot of streamers and stuff played a long time ago.
It was like Outlast.
Yes, that one.
Maybe Outlast.
That was apparently a big thing as well.
Luigi's Mansion?
Is that really scary though?
Or is it just like, heh heh, it's a little spooky spooky.
There's some cobwebs.
Some spiders, you know, and...
Heh heh.
Yeah, it's not really scary though, is it?
It's just a horror vibe, I guess.
Yeah, I knew it.
Dead Space?
Is that a horror game though?
I always thought that would be like a sci-fi shooter.
More than anything.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Dude, speaking of GTA 6.
I was thinking of actually playing it on release.
I don't know if I should, should I?
I've never done that.
Could be kind of cool to do, because it's like a big event, right?
Everyone's gonna be playing it.
It's probably the biggest game release of all time.
I feel like I would be missing out, not joining in on that.
A part of me is like, but it's gonna come out on PC, you know?
And I can play it in 4K and fucking 120 frames.
But then again, I could just replay it.
Yeah, I know I'd need a console.
It would be on console, yeah, yeah.
Grand Theft Auto San Andreas.
I used to play it out on PlayStation when it came out, and it was amazing.
And then it came out on PC, and I played it again, and it was, once again, amazing.
And I played it with a keyboard and mouse, and it was so much better.
Like, it was so much better on keyboard and mouse.
I am a dork when it comes to controller.
Like, I just can't aim for shit with that.
I'm so bad with it.
My brain is mouse-coded, for sure.
Yeah, San Andreas was incredible.
It's such a good game.
I used to play with my friend, and on PlayStation, you could even play co-op.
Which is kind of blowing my mind.
You know, you could play two characters on the same screen.
That was, like, part of the whole experience back then.
I almost forgot about that, but yeah, I did that.
What are you playing Detroit on?
Uh, PC.
But I'm using a controller.
Because, like, a third-person, like, story game, you know?
It's more comfortable to just sit back with a controller.
You still know the cheat codes?
I don't.
But I used to know them by heart.
I would spawn freaking airplanes and tanks.
And, uh, some other things, you know?
It was the best.
Man.
Good times.
Oh, I was a cheater, for sure.
Do you still know the cheat codes?
Some of them, like, it wasn't, like, up-down.
Oh, yeah, it was, actually.
It was, like, left-down, up-right.
Something like that.
That was the combination, you know?
Yeah, it was, like, a bonus content thing.
When you wanted to just fuck around in the world and run from cops or go on a killing spree or something.
Dude, I had so much trouble with the flying missions in the desert.
I remember I just...
I had to get gold star or gold medal in all of those.
And it was so difficult to do.
Man, it was difficult.
Some of them were really bullshit, too, I remember.
I was thinking about that, Frank.
Maybe I'll do, uh, Mario 64, actually.
I still haven't gotten all the stars, you know?
I think I got to, like, 90 or 100 back in the day with my family.
Never did manage to find them all.
Alright, I'm out of here, guys.
Thank you so much for showing up to this disaster of a stream that somehow turned into a wonderful ending there.
It was fun.
Good to be back.
The day after tomorrow, we're gonna continue our Doki Doki Literature Club.
Oh, God, help me.
Uh, we'll see if we can finish the game that day.
We'll see what happens.
If not, uh, I am intent on...
finishing it.
So we will finish that game.
No matter what.
Yeah.
I'll see you around.
Bye-bye.